<archimate:BusinessActor
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="MarkLogic"
    id="id-483b1f59aa644765a8a51a82490c36d2"
    documentation="MarkLogic corporation was founded in 2001 with the vision to create a database that was searchable so that organizations could integrate, store, manage, and search their own data in the same way that you search Google.&#xA;&#xA;The founder of MarkLogic is Christopher Lindblad, the Chief Architect of the Ultraseek search engine, which he launched alongside other search pioneers. Chris’ initial patents for MarkLogic focused on storing and searching unstructured XML data, and later patents spanned into multi-model capabilities.&#xA;&#xA;MarkLogic quickly gained prominence as large enterprises faced the challenges of integrating large volumes and varieties data. But, those large enterprises also needed enterprise features. For that reason, MarkLogic’s early product releases were designed with features such as ACID transactions and granular security.&#xA;&#xA;In 2012, Gary Bloom joined MarkLogic as the CEO. Gary was an early employee at Oracle, and led Oracle’s database division through their most significant period of growth in the early 1990’s. Other executives joined MarkLogic to help with product development, bringing experience from Microsoft, Symantec, and other successful enterprise tech companies.&#xA;&#xA;Today, MarkLogic has an impressive list of over 2,500 customers spanning the globe and a dozen offices in the U.S. Europe, and Asia-Pacific.&#xA;&#xA;As the company has grown, one thing never changed—the vision is still to enable organizations to get more value from their data faster. By executing on this vision, the company has established itself as the best data platform for simplifying data integration and the leader of the Data Hub space.&#xA;&#xA;More at : &#xA;https://www.marklogic.com/company/about/&#xA;&#xA;Headquarters&#xA;999 Skyway Road, Suite 200&#xA;San Carlos, CA, 94070&#xA;+1 650 655 2300 (PHONE)&#xA;+1 877 992 8885 (TOLL-FREE)&#xA;&#xA;Paris&#xA;Étoile Saint-Honoré&#xA;23 rue Balzac, 4me étage&#xA;75008 Paris&#xA;France&#xA;+33 1 53 53 67 84 (PHONE)"/>
