<archimate:Product
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="CogitoStudio"
    id="id-b263b759ea1148bf8288d117d44eb2ae"
    documentation="https://expertsystem.com/products/cogito-studio/&#xA;&#xA;Cogito Studio Express est un éditeur d’ontologie qui vous permet de coordonner les processus et les ressources nécessaires à la création, à la gestion, à l’enrichissement et à l’application d’une ontologie à des contenus afin d’enrichir des métadonnées. Accessible par le biais d’une interface conviviale, Cogito Studio Express est l’outil idéal pour les équipes travaillant au développement et au maintien d’une ontologie partagée.&#xA;&#xA;Where language and Artificial Intelligence intersect&#xA;&#xA;Cogito Studio is a fully integrated development environment for building and deploying a custom AI-based text model that leverages the cognitive abilities of the Cogito platform. As the command center for Cogito-powered deployments, Cogito Studio helps organizations and developers to create advanced and unique solutions to extend the scope of intelligent process automation and make knowledge discovery more effective.&#xA;&#xA;Cogito Studio applies the Natural Language Understanding capability of Cogito and a fine-grained text processing configuration to achieve precise comprehension of your content in order to give you complete control over how you access the content and how to use it efficiently and at scale in support of your business operations.&#xA;&#xA;ext analytics model development&#xA;&#xA;Cogito Studio provides advanced linguistic rule writing to support effective entity and relationship extraction and automatic document categorization. You can immediately deploy and optimize the initial rules set to start document categorization. When required, you can simplify and automate the rule writing process through integration with machine learning algorithms.&#xA;Knowledge graph editor&#xA;&#xA;The advanced cognitive capabilities of Cogito Studio allow you to customize your projects by augmenting and enriching the Cogito knowledge graph through the acquisition of Subject Matter Expert Knowledge or through machine learning.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Test bench&#xA;&#xA;Cogito Studio provides sophisticated testing and reporting tools for validating your model against a collection of documents. This allows you to measure regressions and improvements for precision and recall in order to check results than can be quickly improved to match your quality requirements.&#xA;Integrated collaboration&#xA;&#xA;Cogito Studio allows users to run more than one project at the same time and scales on a multi-server environment. It provides extensive scalability in the management of documents in any format.&#xA;&#xA;Brief Cogito Studio: https://expertsystem.com/brief-cogito-studio/&#xA;&#xA;Why enterprise taxonomy and ontology management technology is disruptive: https://expertsystem.com/enterprise-taxonomy-ontology-management/&#xA;&#xA;Knowledge Graph: https://expertsystem.com/learning-center/technology/knowledge-graph/&#xA;&#xA;The truth about machine learning (and deep learning): https://expertsystem.com/truth-machine-learning-deep-learning-2/&#xA;"/>
