<archimate:Product
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Flokzu"
    id="id-8e720b3d8e95488e9b80c928b410342b"
    documentation="https://www.flokzu.com/&#xA;&#xA;What is Flokzu?&#xA;Flokzu is a powerful cloud BPM tool, made agile &amp; friendly. Flokzu is categorized as low-code because it lets you automate business processes &amp; workflows in minutes with an amazing User Interface both in web and mobile. Put your recurring tasks in autopilot. No more looking who's responsible for a task in a complex spreadsheet. &#xA;&#xA;Flokzu allows you to model your processes using the BPMN standard. With one-click deployment, you can immediately run, measure and improve them. Flokzu integrates with your other legacy systems and web applications using REST Web Services and Zapier. And it also includes one of the strongest document manager and search engine in the market for you to find anything.&#xA;&#xA;______________&#xA;More details: &#xA;&#xA;Model your cloud workflow&#xA;Using the international standard BPMN and a simple drag-and-drop interface you can model your cloud workflow according to your organization's reality. Combine tasks, deadlines, time management, business rules, and notifications without writing a single line of code. Deploying and running your processes in minutes/hours (instead of weeks/months) is a key benefit of your cloud BPM.&#xA;&#xA;Customize the form&#xA;Define the form that needs to be completed at each step of the process with an amazing Form Builder. Multiple field types and visibility options can be combined to meet every possible need. Default values, auto-populated content, functions, and scripts to save valuable time and avoid mistakes. Arrange your fields using a grid layout and sections. A well-designed form is key to accomplish an intuitive and flexible cloud workflow.&#xA;&#xA;Execute the process&#xA;A key feature of your cloud BPM is that assignees will receive pending tasks on their Inbox in their PC or mobile. As the process instance moves along the workflow, each task will be assigned to a user or role automatically. Each task will display fields, attachments, and comments. Use filters and searches to quickly find what you need and identify which tasks are more urgent. Reassign tasks when needed and check the audit trail for changes.&#xA;&#xA;Measure and Analyze&#xA;Statistics are key in your cloud BPM initiative. They will show you how your processes are doing: What tasks are currently delayed? Which users/roles have more tasks assigned? Historical data will help you make better decisions: the number of processes launched, how many were completed and which tasks are more time-consuming. Custom Reports let you focus on what matters the most to you and your team. Share them with whoever you want or schedule to send via email (e.g. every week) increasing your cloud workflow efficiency."/>
