<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureSQLEdge"
    id="81f607c9-d323-40b8-afe3-0ad41e6c929a"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/sql-edge/&#xA;Azure SQL Edge PREVIEW&#xA;Small-footprint, edge-optimized data engine with built-in AI&#xA;Simplify edge architecture and application development&#xA;Running on ARM and Intel architecture, Azure SQL Edge—now in public preview—brings the most secure Microsoft SQL engine to the edge. This productivity tool for edge computing combines new capabilities such as data streaming and time series with in-database machine learning and graph features. Develop your application once and deploy anywhere across the edge, your datacenter, and Azure.&#xA;&#xA;Small-footprint container running in ARM- and x64-based devices in a connected or disconnected environment&#xA;&#xA;Built-in data streaming and time series, with in-database machine learning and graph features for low-latency analytics&#xA;&#xA;Processes data at the edge before forwarding it to your datacenter and cloud storage to optimize network bandwidth and cost&#xA;&#xA;Deployment and updates from Azure or your enterprise portal for consistent security and turnkey management&#xA;&#xA;Use your choice of platform&#xA;Expand device architecture coverage to include ARM-based devices on top of x64-based architecture. Choose either Windows or Linux as the operating system, and use Kubernetes to orchestrate your device infrastructure for better efficiency and automation. Run SQL Edge connected or offline to support various edge environments.&#xA;&#xA;See an ARM-based container in action&#xA;Store and analyze time-series dataPlaying&#xA;Store and analyze time-series data&#xA;SQL Edge is optimized for edge workloads such as IoT to stream, store, and analyze time-series data. Analyze data while it’s being streamed using time-windowing, aggregation, and filtering capabilities, and achieve deeper insights by combining data types such as time-series and graph.&#xA;&#xA;Download the infographic&#xA;&#xA;Conduct real-time scoring at the Edge with built-in AI&#xA;Detect anomalies and apply business logic at the edge using the built-in machine learning (ML) capabilities. Choose from popular ML languages and convert using Open Neural Network Exchange (ONNX) to process time-series, graph, and other types of data. Put your cloud-trained models on the edge to perform real-time analytics on streaming data.&#xA;&#xA;Watch a demo on real-time analytics over time-series data&#xA;Enjoy turnkey management&#xA;You don’t need an army of database administrators to install and manage SQL Edge on all your edge devices. Create and deploy the container from a single management portal, and update the container and data schema based on your security-management and business needs.&#xA;&#xA;Get unparalleled performance and security&#xA;Built on the same code base as SQL Server and SQL Database, Azure SQL Edge uses the same high-performing and secure engine to answer the demands of edge computing. Get flexible high availability and disaster recovery using Always On with Kubernetes, and protect data on your edge devices using industry-leading security tools such as transparent data encryption, data masking, and Always Encrypted.&#xA;&#xA;Simplify your edge architecture&#xA;Use a single container for your local streaming, storage, and machine learning. Because the surface area is the same as Azure SQL Database and SQL Server running on-premises, SQL Edge extends a consistent application development and management experience to the edge. Develop once and run your applications wherever you need.&#xA;&#xA;Frequently asked questions about Azure SQL Edge&#xA;How do I get a public preview of Azure SQL Edge?&#xA;How much does it cost? Does it offer the same purchase model as SQL Database?&#xA;What type of device and operating system does it support?&#xA;Does it support offline deployment models independent of Azure IoT Edge?&#xA;How is Azure SQL Edge different from Azure Stream Analytics?&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/InternetOfThings/SQLEdge.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x30"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
