<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AnomalyDectector"
    id="96bc129d-c95b-4adf-a265-b8cd1ad74c8a"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cognitive-services/anomaly-detector/&#xA;&#xA;Anomaly Detector PREVIEW&#xA;An AI service that helps you foresee problems before they occur&#xA;&#xA;Boost your business systems’ reliability with early problem detection&#xA;Easily embed anomaly detection capabilities into your apps so users can quickly identify problems. Through an API, Anomaly Detector Preview ingests time-series data of all types and selects the best-fitting detection model for your data to ensure high accuracy. Customize the service to detect any level of anomaly and deploy it where you need it most -- from the cloud to the intelligent edge with containers. Azure is the only major cloud provider that offers anomaly detection as an AI service.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Powerful inference engine looks at your time-series data set and automatically selects the right algorithm to maximize accuracy for your scenario&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Automatic detection eliminates the need for labeled training data. Save time and stay focused on fixing problems as soon as they surface&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Customizable settings let you fine-tune sensitivity to potential anomalies based on your business’s risk profile&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Speed your time to insights&#xA;&#xA;Fast-track your problem solving with simple setup in the Azure portal and real-time anomaly detection. All it takes is three lines of code.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Detect problems for virtually any scenario&#xA;There are many types of time-series data—and no one algorithm fits them all. Anomaly Detector looks at your time-series data set and automatically selects the best algorithm from the model gallery to ensure high accuracy for your specific scenario: business incidents, monitoring IoT device traffic, managing fraud, responding to changing markets, and more.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Trusted by Microsoft Azure, Office, Windows, and Bing&#xA;Monitor your product and service health, and deliver reliable customer experiences, using the same anomaly detection service that more than 200 Microsoft product teams rely on.&#xA;&#xA;GA-Insights&#xA;&quot;Anomaly Detector has been pivotal in supporting our customers, monitoring their business metrics 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Already we've used the service to alert hundreds of businesses to changes in their data, ranging from e-commerce conversion rates to revenue alerts. Our customers get an enriched view of their analytics, giving them early opportunity to act on their data – an opportunity that they never had previously.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;Patrick McCurley, Founder, GA-Insights&#xA;Read more&#xA;Industry-leading security for the enterprise&#xA;&#xA;Microsoft invests over USD 1 billion annually on cyber security research and development.&#xA;We employ more than 3,500 security experts who are completely focused on securing your data and privacy.&#xA;Azure has more certifications than any other cloud provider. View the comprehensive list.&#xA;Learn more about our compliance and certifications&#xA;Documentation and quickstarts&#xA;Start using Anomaly Detector&#xA;Learn how to embed anomaly detection capabilities into your apps.&#xA;&#xA;Explore the documentation&#xA;Anomaly Detector in containers&#xA;Learn how it works&#xA;Watch these episodes of the AI Show for a guided walkthrough on setting up Anomaly Detector:&#xA;&#xA;Episode 1: Introducing Anomaly Detector&#xA;Episode 2: Bring Anomaly Detector on premises&#xA;Episode 3: Best practices&#xA;Episode 4: Anomaly detection for streaming data&#xA;Fine-tune risk sensitivity&#xA;Adjust the risk sensitivity of the anomaly detection algorithm using a single parameter.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about this feature&#xA;Get started in three ste">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/AnomalyDetector.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
