<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="BingCustomSearch"
    id="7e475eae-6be1-4f9c-950e-a9c388df7cbf"
    documentation="An easy-to-use, ad-free, commercial-grade search tool that lets you deliver the results you want&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cognitive-services/bing-custom-search/&#xA;The Bing Custom Search API gives you powerful ranking, a global-scale search index, and document processing with fast, simple setup. The core technology works in four steps—by identifying on-topic sites and images, providing automatic query suggestions, applying the Bing ranker, and delivering relevant search results. Adjust the parameters and access usage insights anytime.&#xA;Powerful search for your domain&#xA;Define the parts of the web you want to draw from so users only see relevant results from the domains, subsites, and web pages you choose. Explore site suggestions to expand the scope of your search domain. And harness the full power of Bing’s global-scale search index to get a holistic view of searches and ranking.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Tailored search for specific content&#xA;Create a compelling search experience for content, such as web pages, images, videos, and even autosuggested words. With Bing Custom Search, promote or filter results to drive the outcome you want.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Customized automatic query completions&#xA;Predefine automatic query suggestions for your content within selected domains. Help users complete their queries faster by adding intelligent type-ahead capabilities to your app or website.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Complete control over search results&#xA;Control ranking, pinning, blocking, boosting, and demoting sites. Share your custom search instances with select individuals in your organization, and quickly test your deployments using the instance staging feature.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Easy launch and refinement&#xA;Quickly and reliably define and adjust the parameters of your search domain without writing a line of code. Render search result layouts using a customizable hosted Bing user experience.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Ad-free, commercial-grade service&#xA;Usage of the Bing Custom Search engine is ad-free, no matter how much or how little of the service you use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Powerful statistics for your Powerful statistics from custom search queries&#xA;Quickly retrieve key insights, such as total query volume, top queries, market distribution of queries, response code distribution, and many others. You can subscribe to Bing Statistics Add-in from Azure Portal.&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/bing-512.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
