<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="TextAnalytics"
    id="adea3fda-6c34-49e4-b6c1-b6ca94c6d0c4"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cognitive-services/text-analytics/&#xA;&#xA;Text Analytics&#xA;An AI service that uncovers insights such as sentiment, entities, and key phrases in unstructured text&#x9;&#xA;&#xA;Extract insights from text&#xA;Discover insights in unstructured text using natural language processing—no machine learning expertise required. Identify key phrases and entities such as people, places, and organizations to understand common topics and trends. Gain a deeper understanding of customer opinions with sentiment analysis. Evaluate text in a wide range of languages.&#xA;&#xA;Broad entity extraction&#xA;Identify important concepts in text, including key phrases and named entities.&#xA;&#xA;Powerful sentiment analysis&#xA;Examine what customers are saying about your brand, and detect sentiment around specific topics.&#xA;&#xA;Robust language detection&#xA;Evaluate text input in a wide range of languages.&#xA;&#xA;Flexible deployment&#xA;Run Text Analytics anywhere—in the cloud, on-premises, or at the edge in containers.&#xA;&#xA;We went to Contoso Steakhouse located at midtown NYC last week for a dinner party, and we adore the spot! They provide marvelous food and they have a great menu. The chief cook happens to be the owner (I think his name is John Doe) and he is super nice, coming out of the kitchen and greeted us all. We enjoyed very much dining in the place! The Sirloin steak I ordered was tender and juicy, and the place was impeccably clean. You can even pre-order from their online menu at www.contososteakhouse.com, call 312-555-0176 or send email to order@contososteakhouse.com! The only complaint I have is the food didn't come fast enough. Overall I highly recommend it!&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;iLINKED ENTITIES:&#x9;We went to Contoso Steakhouse located at midtown NYC last week for a dinner party, and we adore the spot! They provide marvelous food and they have a great menu. The chief cook happens to be the owner (I think his name is John Doe) and he is super nice, coming out of the kitchen and greeted us all. We enjoyed very much dining in the place! The Sirloin steak I ordered was tender and juicy, and the place was impeccably clean. You can even pre-order from their online menu at www.contososteakhouse.com, call 312-555-0176 or send email to order@contososteakhouse.com! The only complaint I have is the food didn't come fast enough. Overall I highly recommend it!&#xA;Identify and categorize important concepts&#xA;Classify a broad range of entities in text, such as people, places, organizations, date/time, and percentages, using named entity recognition. Detect and extract more than 100 types of personally identifiable information (PII) and more than 80 types of protected health information (PHI) in documents. Speed your time to insights with prebuilt entity extraction models.&#xA;&#xA;Extract key phrases in unstructured text&#xA;Quickly evaluate and identify the main points in unstructured text. Get a list of relevant phrases that best describe the subject of each record using key phrase extraction. Easily pull and organize information to make sense of important topics and trends.&#xA;&#xA;Better understand customer perception&#xA;Detect positive and negative sentiment in social media, customer reviews, and other sources to get a pulse on your brand.&#xA;&#xA;Deploy anywhere, from the cloud to the edge&#xA;Run Text Analytics wherever your data resides. Build applications that are optimized for both robust cloud capabilities and edge locality using containers.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/TextAnalytics.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
