<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="QNAMarker"
    id="8fe40303-59b8-4b43-b814-edcb482a2eb9"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cognitive-services/qna-maker/&#xA;&#xA;QnA Maker&#xA;Go from semi-structured content to bot in minutes&#xA;&#xA;Quickly create a conversational layer over your data&#xA;QnA Maker is a cloud-based API service that lets you create a conversational question-and-answer layer over your existing data. Use it to build a knowledge base by extracting questions and answers from your semi-structured content, including FAQs, manuals, and documents. Answer users’ questions with the best answers from the QnAs in your knowledge base—automatically. Your knowledge base gets smarter, too, as it continually learns from user behavior.&#xA;&#xA;Automatically extract question-answer pairs from semi-structured content, including FAQs, product manuals, guidelines, support documents, and policies.&#xA;&#xA;Improve your knowledge base with suggestions for alternative questions. Add or reject them based on their relevance.&#xA;&#xA;Easily create, edit, and train complex multiturn conversations in the QnA Maker portal or using REST APIs.&#xA;&#xA;Create and publish a bot in Teams, Skype, or elsewhere; no code experience required. Simply upload a semi-structured document or URL.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Add personality to your bot using chit-chat&#xA;Make your bot more conversational by adding a pre-populated chit-chat dataset. Choose a persona that’s professional, witty, friendly, caring, or enthusiastic.&#xA;&#xA;Support rich data and dynamically manage content&#xA;You can add rich content to your knowledge base with the new in-built rich text editor in QnA Maker. You can also use Markdown’s full capability to author answers directly in QnA Maker or upload a knowledge base that includes rich content.&#xA;&#xA;Learn about rich content&#xA;Scale to meet your business and compliance needs&#xA;QnA Maker service is a hosted model, so you can choose product tiers according to your size and throughput needs and feel secure knowing all components are within your Azure compliance boundary.&#xA;&#xA;Learn about QnA Maker architecture&#xA;Chat in more than 50 languages&#xA;You can select the language of your QnA service while creating the first knowledge base. All the subsequent knowledge bases in a QnA Maker resource will be in the same language.&#xA;&#xA;Learn about supported languages">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/QnAMarker.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
