<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="VideoIndexer"
    id="62855125-2042-4165-a2f3-9d147c5649b4"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/media-services/video-indexer/&#xA;Video Indexer&#xA;Automatically extract advanced metadata from video and audio content&#xA;Gain valuable insights from your video and audio files&#xA;Automatically extract metadata—such as spoken words, written text, faces, speakers, celebrities, emotions, topics, brands, and scenes—from video and audio files. Access the data within your application or infrastructure, make it more discoverable, and use it to create new over-the-top (OTT) experiences and monetization opportunities. Try the web experience and API with a free trial.&#xA;&#xA;Multichannel pipeline orchestrates visual and auditory cues and incorporates insights into a shared timeline&#xA;&#xA;Easy to evaluate and integrate, and available via web portal, web widgets, and REST APIs&#xA;&#xA;Intuitive customization to train and fine-tune selected AI models, improve content accuracy, and configure your account&#xA;&#xA;Helps you meet compliance obligations for HIPAA, SOC, ISO, FedRAMP, HITRUST, PCI, and more&#xA;&#xA;Improve content discoverability and performance&#xA;Enhance your search experiences by using the metadata automatically extracted from your content. Multichannel analysis provides information to perform a more effective search across your media archive and within each file. Search by person, object, visual text, spoken word, entity, or emotion.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Enhance user engagement&#xA;Apply the extracted metadata to improve user experience. Use speech transcription and translation to easily add closed captioning in multiple languages, fine-tune recommendation algorithms based on objects and people that appear in a video, and automatically create clips from sections featuring a particular person. Reuse the Video Indexer portal widgets on your own applications without building the underlying infrastructure.&#xA;&#xA;Generate fresh content in minutes&#xA;Create new media from existing content by using the AI-based video editor. Find the right media content in your library, locate the pieces you’re interested in, and use our award-winning technology to stitch them together into a new video. When you’re happy with the result, render and download the video and use it in your own editing applications or downstream workflows.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/VideoIndexer.jpg"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
