<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="FormRecognizer"
    id="c91e2bf1-3da4-4e94-84a7-79f716bf2224"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cognitive-services/form-recognizer/&#xA;&#xA;Form Recognizer PREVIEW&#xA;The AI-powered document extraction service that understands your forms&#xA;&#xA;Quickly extract text and structure from documents&#xA;Accelerate your business processes by automating information extraction. Form Recognizer applies advanced machine learning to accurately extract text, key/value pairs, and tables from documents. With just a few samples, Form Recognizer tailors its understanding to your documents, both on-premises and in the cloud. Turn forms into usable data at a fraction of the time and cost, so you can focus more time acting on the information rather than compiling it.&#xA;&#xA;Simple extraction&#xA;Easily pull data and organize information with prebuilt and custom features—no manual labeling required.&#xA;&#xA;Customized results&#xA;Get output tailored to your layouts with automatic custom extraction, and improve it with human feedback.&#xA;&#xA;Flexible deployment&#xA;Ingest data from the cloud to the edge and apply to search indexes, business automation workflows, and more.&#xA;&#xA;Built-in security&#xA;Rely on enterprise-grade security and privacy applied to both your data and any trained models.&#xA;&#xA;Easily extract text and structure, with simple REST API&#xA;Accurately extract text, key/value pairs, and tables from documents, forms, and receipts, without manual labeling by document type or intensive coding or maintenance. Form Recognizer uses pre-built and unsupervised learning components to understand the layout and relationships between fields and entries in your documents, to pull information in an organized manner.&#xA;&#xA;Customize extraction to your forms&#xA;When you’re working with documents that deviate from traditional formats, like industry-specific materials, you often need to build your own solution. The custom extraction capabilities in Form Recognizer help you overcome this challenge by training on your own data based on just five documents. Not only is the first output more reliable and tailored to your needs, but also you can provide human inputs to create a highly accurate model customized to your forms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Apply Form Recognizer anywhere, from the cloud to the edge&#xA;Recognize forms on the edge, on-premises, and in the cloud with container support in Azure Cognitive Services. The portable architecture can be deployed directly to Azure Kubernetes Service or Azure Container Instances, or to a Kubernetes cluster deployed to Azure Stack. Use the REST interface of the Form Recognizer API to then integrate into cognitive search indexes, automate business processes, and create custom workflows for your business.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Analyze forms and documents&#xA;Make data-driven decisions by extracting data from tables and forms and putting it into your data visualization service for analysis.&#xA;&#xA;Create intelligent search indexes&#xA;Easily find specific information in your documents and forms, such as total accounts payable, by integrating Form Recognizer with Azure Cognitive Search.&#xA;&#xA;Automate business workflows&#xA;Extract text, key-value pairs, and tables from forms and receipts, and pipe them into your back-end systems to perform tasks such as claim, invoice, and receipt processing.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/form_recognizer_logo.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
