<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="LanguageUnderstanding"
    id="1f1591fc-bf7d-49b6-ab81-8b28c9045623"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cognitive-services/language-understanding-intelligent-service/&#xA;&#xA;Language Understanding&#xA;An AI service that allows users to interact with your applications, bots, and IoT devices by using natural language.&#xA;&#xA;Add custom natural language understanding to your apps&#xA;Build applications capable of understanding natural language. Using machine teaching technology and our visual user interface, developers and subject matter experts can build custom machine-learned language models that interprets user goals and extracts key information from conversational phrases—all without any machine learning experience.&#xA;&#xA;Consume your custom language models in the cloud or on premises in containers.&#xA;Create custom language models specific to your use case with developer tools and portal experience to simplify labeling.&#xA;&#xA;Build natural language processing models with no machine learning experience required.&#xA;&#xA;Run Language Understanding anywhere—in the cloud, on premises, and on the edge with containers.&#xA;&#xA;Rely on enterprise-grade security and privacy applied to both your data and any trained models.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Quickly build a custom language solution&#xA;Machine teaching technology enables you to get started without labeled data and to train models interactively to accelerate your development. We provide prebuilt entities, features, and applications to jump start your project.&#xA;&#xA;Read this guide on getting started&#xA;&#xA;Intuitively teach language models&#xA;Using machine teaching techniques, you teach language models like you would teach a person. No machine learning expertise is needed. The simple, iterative process and visual interface makes it simpler than ever before.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about machine teaching&#xA;Always learning and improving&#xA;Language Understanding enables developers to seamlessly improve language models over time based on real traffic.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about active learning&#xA;Build a comprehensive natural language solution&#xA;Integrate seamlessly with Azure Cognitive Services like Text Analytics and Speech, as well as Azure Bot Service for an end-to-end conversational solution.&#xA;&#xA;Add language understanding to your bot&#xA;Enterprise-ready, available worldwide&#xA;Language Understanding scales to meet enterprise quality and performance needs and meets international compliance standards including ISO, HIPAA, SOC, and FedRAMP.&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/azure language understanding.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
