<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Personalizer"
    id="ca715e5c-7081-4624-8fb1-6c5c4310b545"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cognitive-services/personalizer/&#xA;Personalizer&#xA;An award-winning AI service that delivers a personalized, relevant experience for every user&#xA;Create rich, tailored interactions&#xA;Boost usability and user satisfaction with reinforcement learning–based capabilities only available through Azure. Prioritize relevant content, layouts, and conversations through an easy-to-use API. Use Personalizer as a standalone personalization solution or to complement an existing solution—with no machine learning expertise required.&#xA;Automatic model optimization based on reinforcement learning, allowing AI to achieve the goals you set&#xA;&#xA;Apprentice mode provides a smooth transition by only letting Personalizer interact with users after the service reaches a level of confidence in matching the performance of your existing solution&#xA;&#xA;User-friendly interface to monitor and adjust the learning loop according to your parameters and KPIs&#xA;&#xA;No machine-learning expertise required&#xA;&#xA;Improve user experiences with real-time learning&#xA;Give users relevant experiences that improve over time, based on their behavior. Unlike recommendation engines that offer a few options from a large catalog, Personalizer presents the single best outcome for a user, every time they interact with your app.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Get up and running quickly&#xA;Embed Personalizer by adding two lines of code. Easily inspect the accuracy of predictions and optimize as needed. Personalizer works with your data in any form. Start with no data or tap into you’re an existing dataset to jump-start reinforcement learning.&#xA;&#xA;Once embedded, Personalizer can skip the learning curve with apprentice mode. When the feature is switched on, the service learns alongside your existing solution without being exposed to users until it meets your performance threshold.&#xA;&#xA;See more about apprentice mode&#xA;&#xA;Easily gauge how it's working&#xA;Interpret and evaluate Personalizer through the interface. Validate results by reproducing them, and gauge effectiveness of parameters with a stack-ranked view. For example, evaluate the impact of age, gender, and time of day on content engagement.&#xA;&#xA;Evaluate your models&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/Personalizer.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
