<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Encoding"
    id="e5d05a10-89f5-4157-8787-5f7a586cabeb"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/media-services/encoding/&#xA;&#xA;Encoding&#xA;Studio-grade encoding at cloud scale&#xA;&#xA;Encode to multiple formats&#xA;Scalable batch processing&#xA;Thumbnail, overlay, stitching, and clip generation&#xA;High-performance encoding&#xA;Web, professional, and broadcast workflow support&#xA;ISO- and CDSA-certified highly-secure encoding platform&#xA;Live encoding in the cloud&#xA;Live encoding expands on the industry-proven live cloud platform, and can be combined with dynamic packaging, dynamic encryption, sub-clipping, dynamic manifest manipulation, ad marker insertion, and seamless live-to-on-demand capabilities, to build comprehensive live and cloud DVR workflows. Common use cases include event-based streaming with dynamic ad insertion and live streaming with cloud DVR requirements. Live encoding has been used to power some of the largest events on the planet such as Super Bowl 2015 and the 2014 Sochi Winter Olympics.&#xA;Scalable cloud encoding with high performance&#xA;Quickly burst your demanding web- or studio-grade encoding workflows through the cloud. Submit your encoding jobs to the cloud for batch processing on our high-performance computers. You control the performance level and the number of concurrent encoding tasks.&#xA;Highly-secure encoding workflows for web developers, broadcasters, and studios&#xA;From simple web delivery for HTML5 to complex media decision logic that solves demanding studio workflows, the Media Encoder feature of Azure Media Services allows you to define your own encoding workflows. Use desktop tools, like Azure Media Explorer and our advanced graphical Workflow Designer, to define an encoding workflow that meets your business needs and then execute it at scale.&#xA;Pay for what you encode&#xA;Take advantage of the full breadth of our encoding features, but only pay for what you use. Our pricing is based on the duration (minutes) of output, so your bill is easy to understand and calculate, whatever features or encoding options you choose. Scale up and down as your business or workflow demands.&#xA;Encode once and deliver everywhere&#xA;For smooth content delivery across multiple devices, encode all of your content into standard multiple bitrate MP4 files, and deliver them dynamically to the latest adaptive bitrate streaming protocols. Adaptive bitrate streaming gives your customers a better experience by adjusting video playback to meet the demands of their available bandwidth. This means no more buffered messages and a smooth, professional playback experience from the cloud.&#xA;Multiple format support&#xA;We provide you with a wide range of support for the most popular input file formats. Our Standard encoder supports a wide range of web delivery formats, and our Premium encoder supports an even wider range of broadcast and studio file formats to meet the demands of the video industry.&#xA;Save money on encoding and storage with dynamic packaging&#xA;By default, all of our encoding presets create standard MP4 multi-bitrate files, which saves you money on storage and reduces the duplication of encoding costs. You only need to encode and store files in standards-based MP4 file format, and we convert them on the fly into your favorite streaming protocols. Simply add a Streaming Reserved Unit and deliver your files in MPEG-DASH, Apple HTTP Live Streaming (HLS), and Microsoft Smooth Streaming without re-encoding them. To avoid repackaging, you can even add encryption on the fly.&#xA;Advanced encoding features&#xA;Media Encoder gives you thumbnail generation, image and audio overlays, sub-clip creation, and multiple-clip stitching. Use the Workflow Designer to build complex encoding presets that can take specified actions based on metadata from the incoming source file or your own custom recipes."/>
