<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureRTOS"
    id="2228ced5-ab29-4fd7-8694-20fa8d0b8b05"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/rtos/&#xA;Azure RTOS&#xA;Get high-performance devices to market faster and at lower cost&#xA;&#xA;Embedded IoT device development made easy&#xA;Azure RTOS is an embedded development suite including a small but powerful operating system that provides reliable, ultra-fast performance for resource-constrained devices. It’s easy-to-use and market-proven, having been deployed on more than 6.2 billion devices worldwide. Azure RTOS supports the most popular 32-bit microcontrollers and embedded development tools, so you can make the most of your team’s existing skills.&#xA;&#xA;What is a RTOS?&#xA;&#xA;Predictably fast performance and a remarkably small footprint&#xA;&#xA;Easily connect to cloud and local networks, develop durable flash file systems, and design elegant user interfaces&#xA;&#xA;Seamlessly connect the most popular MCUs and MPUs to the power of Azure IoT&#xA;&#xA;Code that has been certified to meet stringent industry safety and security standards&#xA;&#xA;Azure RTOS components&#xA;Azure RTOS ThreadX&#xA;Azure RTOS FileX&#xA;Azure RTOS GUIX Studio and GUIX&#xA;Azure RTOS TraceX&#xA;Azure RTOS NetX&#xA;Azure RTOS NetX Duo&#xA;Azure RTOS USBX&#xA;&#xA;Azure RTOS ThreadX&#xA;This advanced real-time operating system (RTOS) is designed specifically for deeply embedded applications. Among the multiple benefits it provides are real-time multithreading, inter-thread communication and synchronization, and memory management. Azure RTOS ThreadX has many advanced features, including picokernel architecture, preemption threshold, event chaining, and a rich set of system services.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Reliable, real-time performance for resource-constrained devices&#xA;Achieve ultra-fast, predictable run-time performance with minimum resource consumption. Azure RTOS ThreadX offers sub-microsecond context switching, while Azure RTOS NetX Duo offers near-wire-speed network performance. All components are designed to be deterministic and perform in a fast, predictable manner, regardless of system load.&#xA;&#xA;Preemption-threshold scheduling&#xA;Event chaining&#xA;Access to source code with simple licensing options&#xA;The full source code for all Azure RTOS components is available on GitHub to test and explore. When you’re ready to take your code into production, there’s no charge for the production license if deploying to pre-licensed devices. Simple licensing options are available for all other devices.&#xA;&#xA;Access Azure RTOS code on GitHub&#xA;See a list of pre-licensed devices&#xA;High-quality, safety-certified code, right out of the box&#xA;Clean, clear code is easier to use and maintain and can lower total cost of ownership. Most safety-related certifications require you to submit the complete source code for your software, including the RTOS. With Azure RTOS, you not only get high-quality code—you can also access full reports that verify the code meets stringent requirements that govern automotive, railway, medical, energy, and consumer safety standards.&#xA;&#xA;Evaluating source code quality in an RTOS&#xA;Reduce the complexity of connecting to the cloud&#xA;Devices are becoming smarter and more powerful than ever. They can collect data and act on it, learn, and make predictions—but only if they’re connected to a robust cloud service. Transitioning to the Internet of Things can feel overwhelming. We’ve made it easy for you. Azure RTOS is seamlessly integrated with Azure IoT so you can connect, monitor, and control your IoT products. Connect via IoT protocols, reference templates, or IoT Plug and Play with the Azure IoT device SDK.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about Azure IoT&#xA;Security for real-time embedded applications&#xA;Azure RTOS provides IP and socket-layer security via industry standard protocols and compliance standards. In addition, Azure RTOS uses hardware cryptographic and memory protection capabilities.&#xA;&#xA;Supports IP layer security (IPsec) and socket layer security (TLS and DTLS) protocols&#xA;&#xA;Methodically tested and certified to meet international security assurance requirements&#xA;&#xA;Integrated with Azure Security Center to detect threats and remediate issues before they’re exploited&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about Azure IoT Security&#xA;Azure RTOS hardware partners&#xA;These partners will provide integrated solutions to help you quickly start prototyping and developing enterprise-ready solutions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Microchip Technology&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;NXP Semiconductors&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Qualcomm&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Renesas Electronics&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;STMicroelectronics&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Azure RTOS pricing&#xA;Robust components, one simple license.&#xA;&#xA;No cost for testing and exploring of source code&#xA;No cost for production licenses when deployed to pre-licensed devices&#xA;Simple annual licensing for all other devices&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/InternetOfThings/RTOS.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
