<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureVPNGateway"
    id="1713a1b7-dae6-408d-bf8e-3ba73a734f41"
    documentation="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-about-vpngateways&#xA;A VPN gateway is a specific type of virtual network gateway that is used to send encrypted traffic between an Azure virtual network and an on-premises location over the public Internet. You can also use a VPN gateway to send encrypted traffic between Azure virtual networks over the Microsoft network. Each virtual network can have only one VPN gateway. However, you can create multiple connections to the same VPN gateway. When you create multiple connections to the same VPN gateway, all VPN tunnels share the available gateway bandwidth.&#xA;&#xA;What is a virtual network gateway?&#xA;A virtual network gateway is composed of two or more VMs that are deployed to a specific subnet you create called the gateway subnet. Virtual network gateway VMs contain routing tables and run specific gateway services. These VMs are created when you create the virtual network gateway. You can't directly configure the VMs that are part of the virtual network gateway.&#xA;One setting that you configure for a virtual network gateway is the gateway type. Gateway type specifies how the virtual network gateway will be used and the actions that the gateway takes. The gateway type 'Vpn' specifies that the type of virtual network gateway created is a 'VPN gateway', rather than an ExpressRoute gateway. A virtual network can have two virtual network gateways; one VPN gateway and one ExpressRoute gateway - as is the case with coexisting connection configurations. For more information, see Gateway types.&#xA;VPN gateways can be deployed in Azure Availability Zones. This brings resiliency, scalability, and higher availability to virtual network gateways. Deploying gateways in Azure Availability Zones physically and logically separates gateways within a region, while protecting your on-premises network connectivity to Azure from zone-level failures. see About zone-redundant virtual network gateways in Azure Availability Zones&#xA;Creating a virtual network gateway can take up to 45 minutes to complete. When you create a virtual network gateway, gateway VMs are deployed to the gateway subnet and configured with the settings that you specify. After you create a VPN gateway, you can create an IPsec/IKE VPN tunnel connection between that VPN gateway and another VPN gateway (VNet-to-VNet), or create a cross-premises IPsec/IKE VPN tunnel connection between the VPN gateway and an on-premises VPN device (Site-to-Site). You can also create a Point-to-Site VPN connection (VPN over OpenVPN, IKEv2, or SSTP), which lets you connect to your virtual network from a remote location, such as from a conference or from home.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Networking/AzureVPNGateway.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
