<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureServiceBus"
    id="01f3134f-6c2f-49df-bf50-5b2deae68ec8"
    documentation="Reliable cloud messaging as a service (MaaS) and simple hybrid integration&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/service-bus/&#xA;Build reliable and elastic cloud apps with messaging&#xA;Protect your application from temporary spikes in traffic&#xA;Decouple your applications from each other&#xA;Connect your existing on-premises systems to cloud solutions&#xA;Distribute messages to multiple independent back-end systems&#xA;Scale out ordered messaging to multiple readers&#xA;&#xA;Simplify enterprise cloud messaging&#xA;Depend on Azure Service Bus when you need highly-reliable cloud messaging service between applications and services, even when one or more is offline. Available in every Azure region, this fully-managed service eliminates the burdens of server management and licensing. Asynchronous operations give you flexible, brokered messaging between client and server, along with structured first-in, first-out (FIFO) messaging, and publish/subscribe capabilities—excellent for tasks like order processing.&#xA;&#xA;Build scalable cloud solutions&#xA;Asynchronous messaging patterns are the cornerstone of durable applications—they give you the power to scale reliably. Integrate cloud resources such as Azure SQL Database, Azure Storage, and Web Apps, with Service Bus messaging to get smooth operation under variable loads, and the durability to survive intermittent failures.&#xA;&#xA;Implement complex messaging workflows&#xA;Build durable messaging topologies with complex routing and increase overall availability. Use Service Bus to deliver messages to multiple subscribers and fan out message delivery at scale to downstream systems.&#xA;&#xA;Enable highly-secure communication across hybrid cloud solutions&#xA;Access existing assets—wherever they are—without complex firewall, network, or VPN configuration, and use the Hybrid Connections feature within Service Bus Relay. These services give you enhanced authentication and connectivity through the cloud, and the ability to see and monitor activity.&#xA;&#xA;Easily allow multiple apps to share one connection&#xA;Keep your data where it is on-premises, and use the Hybrid Connections feature within Service Bus Relay to enable access from the cloud or anywhere through a single, secure connection.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Integration/AzureServiceBus.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
