<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureTimeSeriesInsight"
    id="bb554505-4269-4d5a-9277-deb8e6e90a3a"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/time-series-insights/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Time Series Insights&#xA;End-to-end IoT analytics platform to monitor, analyze, and visualize your industrial IoT data at scale&#xA;&#xA;Start free &#xA;Product overview&#xA;Features&#xA;Security&#xA;Pricing&#xA;Documentation&#xA;Customer stories&#xA;FAQs&#xA;Free account &#xA;Turn IoT data into actionable insights&#xA;Improve operations and decision-making with decades of IoT data delivered with rich visualization and a turnkey experience. Use real-time data insights and interactive analytics to accelerate IoT data use throughout your organization.&#xA;&#xA;IoT-ready with instant data ingestion, requiring minimal to no data preparation&#xA;&#xA;Warm and cold data analytics for ad-hoc interactive and historical operational analysis&#xA;&#xA;Powerful visualization of asset-based IoT data for context-based exploration&#xA;&#xA;Contextualization of data based on your IoT model, with nesting menus showing hierarchies, relationships, and properties&#xA;&#xA;Accelerate the use of IoT analytics&#xA;From data ingestion to analysis, customize the IoT analytics platform to your needs.&#xA;&#xA;Collect&#xA;&#xA;Store&#xA;&#xA;Model&#xA;&#xA;Analyze&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Collect&#xA;&#xA;Your assets—such as sensors, equipment, and buildings—are constantly streaming new information. Easily ingest all your IoT data into Time Series Insights with native integrations into Azure IoT Hub and Event Hub. Scale your Time Series Insights platform as your IoT-ingestible data volume grows.&#xA;&#xA;Built for IoT&#xA;Turn disparate data streams into insights and provide context using Time Series Model. From the beginning of your engagement to the full connection of your industrial assets, access near-real-time data streaming and historical data for a complete picture.&#xA;&#xA;See it in action&#xA;&#xA;Inherently scalable&#xA;Uncover new insights as your IoT data grows. Ingest and store billions of IoT events as you scale to hundreds of thousands of assets. With our pay-as-you go pricing, you get an end-to-end industrial IoT analytics platform that matures with your business.&#xA;&#xA;Explore visualization features&#xA;Open and flexible&#xA;Make IoT data accessible to the masses. Use the Time Series Insights explorer for rich visualizations and a turnkey experience. Link industrial IoT data with other business metrics with the native Power BI connector. Build custom dashboards with the open-source data formats, rich APIs, and Javascript SDK.&#xA;&#xA;See our APIs&#xA;What can you build with Time Series Insights?&#xA;Data exploration and visual anomaly detection&#xA;Uncover the causes of abnormalities by analyzing billions of IoT events. Discover hidden trends based on relationships between sensors.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Operational analysis and process efficiency&#xA;Monitor the health, usage, and performance of your assets to drive operational efficiency at scale. Time Series Insights gives you the capacity to manage billions of data events from diverse and unpredictable IoT devices, without compromising performance.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Advanced analytics with Azure IoT&#xA;Integrate Time Series Insights with advanced analytics services, such as Azure Machine Learning, Azure Databricks, Apache Spark, and others. Compare real-time data against your models to quickly discover new patterns or potential issues.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;&#xA;Turn data into insights&#xA;Explore five key factors that are helping customers achieve operational intelligence with time series data. Get best practices and tips from customers using IoT data to transform their organizations.&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/InternetOfThings/TimeSeriesInsight.jpg"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
