<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDigitalTwins"
    id="c943bbfd-e4a3-45ea-897e-349f4d00d495"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/digital-twins/&#xA;Azure Digital Twins&#xA;A service for building advanced IoT spatial intelligence solutions&#xA;&#xA;Build contextually-aware IoT solutions&#xA;&#xA;Azure Digital Twins is an IoT service that helps you create comprehensive models of physical environments. Create spatial intelligence graphs to model the relationships and interactions between people, places, and devices. Query data from a physical space rather than disparate sensors. And, build reusable, highly scalable, spatially aware experiences that link streaming data across the physical and digital world.&#xA;&#xA;Model the relationships between people, places, and devices using the spatial intelligence graph—a virtual representation of your physical environment&#xA;Simplify and accelerate your development process with digital-twin object models that are aligned to your solution’s domain-specific needs&#xA;Build solutions that you can scale securely and reuse for multiple tenants, and create multiple isolated subtenants for added security&#xA;Run custom functions against incoming device data, and improve the customization and automation of device tasks, with advanced compute capabilities&#xA;Build digital-twin solutions that better serve people’s needs&#xA;&#xA;Virtually replicate the physical world by modeling the relationships between people, places, and devices in a spatial intelligence graph. Create uniquely relevant experiences by correlating data across the physical and digital worlds. Discover opportunities to improve consumer experiences, create new efficiencies, and improve the spaces in which people live, work, and play.&#xA;Azure Digital Twins Introduction &#xA;Accelerate and simplify the creation of digital-twin solutions&#xA;&#xA;Save on development costs and quickly deploy your solution to make your space smarter—whether it’s a hospital, a stadium, a factory, or the electrical grid that connects them. Azure Digital Twins offers predefined data schema that are aligned to your solution’s domain-specific needs, simplifying the process and helping you build faster.&#xA;Automate actions in a physical space&#xA;&#xA;Query data in the context of a space rather than from disparate sensors. Define and execute functions that generate notifications or events to specific endpoints within a space, based on telemetry messages from a variety of devices and sensors. These powerful capabilities help you improve the efficiency and conditions of spaces for the people who use them.&#xA;Modernize and scale your business with confidence&#xA;&#xA;Build digital-twin solutions that scale and replicate across multiple tenants. Built-in support for multitenancy and nested tenancy helps secure your customers’ data. Features that help you manage access and identity, such as role-based access control and Azure Active Directory, further highlight our commitment to security, data privacy, and compliance.&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/MixedReality/AzureDigitalTwins.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
