<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureAppService"
    id="99d88a2e-ae0b-4da0-a4ea-38bfbc0f6507"
    documentation="App Service&#xA;Build, deploy, and scale web apps on a fully managed platform&#xA;&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/app-service/&#xA;&#xA;High productivity for both devs and ops: Quickly build, deploy, and scale web apps created with popular frameworks .NET, .NET Core, Node.js, Java, PHP, Ruby, or Python, in containers or running on any operating system. Meet rigorous, enterprise-grade performance, security, and compliance requirements by using the fully managed platform for your operational and monitoring tasks.&#xA;&#xA;Easily build powerful web apps and APIs&#xA;Use popular frameworks including .NET, .NET Core, Java, Node.js, Python, PHP, and Ruby. Deploy them in containers or as code, running on Linux or Windows. Use a fully managed platform that provides management, monitoring, and operational insights to meet rigorous, enterprise-grade performance, security, and compliance requirements. Get unparalleled developer productivity with advanced capabilities such as continuous integration, live-site debugging, and Microsoft Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code IDEs. Tap into prebuilt apps from the Azure Marketplace.&#xA;&#xA;Take control with a fully managed platform&#xA;Run and scale your web apps on Windows or Linux using a fully managed platform to perform infrastructure maintenance, load balancing, and more—all with zero-downtime deployments. Connect your apps to SQL or NoSQL databases, in Azure or in your own datacenter. Easily add custom domains, SSL certificates, single sign-on (SSO), and identity-service integration to your apps. Get detailed performance and application health insights for accelerated troubleshooting.&#xA;&#xA;Host your apps with confidence&#xA;App Service offers an enterprise-grade global datacenter network. Connect your web or mobile apps to enterprise systems or SaaS in minutes. Secure them with Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) integration, and deploy them in the environment of your choice—public cloud, private cloud, virtual network, or on-premises. Easily set up and run apps at scale in the isolated, compliant, and dedicated Azure App Service Environment. Get more secure, high-speed connections to on-premises corporate resources and other Azure resources, and maintain fine-grained control over network traffic.&#xA;&#xA;Migrate your ASP.NET apps in minutes&#xA;Simplify your journey to the cloud by migrating your ASP.NET applications from on-premises to Azure. Quickly and easily assess whether your site could be moved to App Service.&#xA;&#xA;Migrate in three steps:&#xA;Assess your app with an endpoint scan.&#xA;Download the migration assistant.&#xA;Migrate your app.&#xA;&#xA;Turbocharge your apps using Azure solutions: Use App Service with other popular Azure services for functionality your end users will love.&#xA;&#xA;Add search functionality, vision, or speech to your App Service web app using Cognitive Services.&#xA;Globally scale the NoSQL or SQL databases connected to your App Service web app using Azure Cosmos DB.&#xA;Add location, traffic, or routing functionality to your App Service web app using Azure Maps.&#xA;Build serverless apps by integrating your app functionality using Azure Functions, Logic Apps, and API Management capabilities&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Compute/AzureAppService.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
  <properties
      key="Editor"
      value="Microsoft"/>
  <properties
      key="Editor"
      value="Microsoft"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
