<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="StorSimple"
    id="0df1f5d6-3c7b-4368-b412-71281a5a13dc"
    documentation="StorSimple&#xA;An enterprise hybrid cloud storage solution that lowers costs by up to 60%&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/storsimple/&#xA;onsolidate storage infrastructure&#xA;Automate data management across the enterprise&#xA;Accelerate disaster recovery, improve compliance&#xA;Enhance IT agility to support core business&#xA;&#xA;Consolidate storage infrastructure&#xA;Microsoft Azure StorSimple meets the needs of performance- and capacity-centric applications, and gives you a complete hybrid cloud storage solution for enterprises. It’s the best of both worlds—physical arrays for deployments in datacenters and virtual arrays for smaller enterprise environments like remote and branch offices, which require network-attached storage (NAS). Its on-demand infrastructure means you don’t need to set up or maintain costly on-premises equipment for new or special projects. Also, by using local storage for performance, you have the flexibility to retain all volume data locally.&#xA;Automate data management&#xA;Manage your data growth more effectively—StorSimple can automatically archive inactive primary data from on-premises to the cloud to create effortless capacity expansion. Remove the need for separate backup infrastructures with cloud snapshots that provide off-site data protection, and eliminate the need for remote replication of data to a secondary datacenter with cloud storage. Shift your focus from capacity purchases and infrastructure maintenance to meeting business needs.&#xA;Accelerate disaster recovery, improve compliance&#xA;Get reliable and rapid disaster recovery, even for very large volumes. By using software policies instead of tape rotations or backup system capacity, StorSimple gives you immediate data availability during a partial or full disaster recovery. Applications come up faster to accelerate overall recovery and potentially help to save millions of dollars in recovered productivity costs. Most importantly, StorSimple allows you to fine-tune and fix gaps by testing data recovery, and it ensures compliance with corporate policies for data retention and disaster recovery without disrupting daily datacenter operations.&#xA;Enhance IT agility, drive your business&#xA;Speed up your business intelligence and decisions with innovative, rapid data movement from remote/branch offices and datacenters to the cloud. StorSimple increases your operational efficiency, prevents the need to spend IT budgets on unnecessary storage purchases, and significantly reduces IT overhead—helping you to reclaim administrator hours and reduce storage costs by as much as 60%.&#xA;&#xA;StorSimple 8000 Series&#xA;Take a better approach to enterprise storage. Bringing solid state drives (SSDs) and hard disk drives (HDDs) together with cloud storage, StorSimple 8000 Series hybrid arrays take advantage of economical cloud storage for inactive data, while keeping your most mission-critical data on-premises for the highest levels of performance. The result is enterprise hybrid cloud storage that gives you primary storage, backup, archive, integrated data protection, and location-independent disaster recovery. When paired with Microsoft Azure, StorSimple delivers massive scaling of storage infrastructure, prevents constant storage sprawl, and optimizes your total enterprise storage efficiency and costs. The StorSimple Cloud Appliance (8010 and 8020) is a software version of the StorSimple solution in virtual machine form that runs in Azure. The StorSimple 8010 is based on Azure Storage and virtual machines and is a great alternative to single item recovery. The StorSimple 8020 uses Azure Premium Storage and gives you disaster recovery and applications to run in Azure with the StorSimple Cloud Appliance.&#xA;StorSimple Virtual Array&#xA;StorSimple announced the public preview of the on-premises StorSimple Virtual Array. It’s a version of the StorSimple solution in a virtual machine form installed in your remote or branch office. It gives you a cost-effective, lightweight solution for smaller enterprise environments, while still delivering the fundamental value of the StorSimple Hybrid Cloud Storage solution. You can download StorSimple Virtual Array from the StorSimple Manager, on the Azure portal, and installed on a virtual machine configured on a Hyper-V or VMware hypervisor. The StorSimple Virtual Array can be configurable as a NAS (using SMB) or a SAN (using iSCSI) device. It will initially be targeted for file sharing, information worker and collaboration scenarios, and small database workloads using a combination of local and tiered volumes. You manage the StorSimple Virtual Array from the StorSimple Manager service in the Azure portal.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Storage/AzureStorSimple.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
