<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureIotSolutionAccelerator"
    id="a3273e08-45d1-4c19-9f75-5288d6b58a09"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/features/iot-accelerators/&#xA;&#xA;Azure IoT solution accelerators&#xA;Complete, ready-to-deploy solutions for common IoT scenarios&#xA;&#xA;Build with comprehensive IoT cloud solution accelerators&#xA;Kick-start your implementation of common Internet of Things (IoT) scenarios like remote monitoring, industrial IoT (IIoT), predictive maintenance, and device simulation. Get all the required cloud-based services you need—including all required application code—for a successful, efficient, and streamlined build and deployment.&#xA;&#xA;Get started fast: Deploy in minutes and upgrade at your own pace&#xA;&#xA;Customize your solution: Maintain full control of your solution design and tailor already deployed services to meet your needs&#xA;&#xA;Act on new insights: Visualize data in a preconfigured dashboard and set rules to trigger actions through the user interface&#xA;&#xA;Use open source: The open source code base was designed on fully tested architecture and is available on GitHub&#xA;&#xA;Azure IoT for remote monitoring&#xA;Collect and analyze real-time device data to trigger automatic alerts and actions—including performing remote diagnostics and automatically initiating maintenance requests. Use the remote monitoring dashboard to view telemetry from your connected devices, provision new devices, and upgrade firmware on your connected devices.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Try the demo&#xA;Provision the service&#xA;Resources and services used&#xA;Azure IoT for device simulation&#xA;Develop and test your IoT solution on simulated devices using the device simulation solution accelerator. Conduct realistic tests using complex device models to emulate real-world scenarios. Use the device simulation web app to configure and run simulations.&#xA;&#xA;Provision the service&#xA;Resources and services used&#xA;&#xA;Azure IoT for connected factory&#xA;Connect and monitor your industrial assets using standards like OPC-UA with the Azure IoT connected factory solution accelerator. Extract data from brownfield devices to start gathering insights to drive increased performance on the factory floor. Monitor and manage your industrial devices using the connected factory dashboard.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Try the demo&#xA;Provision the service&#xA;Resources and services used&#xA;&#xA;Azure IoT for predictive maintenance&#xA;Analyze streaming data from sensors and devices to predict equipment failures and avoid costly repairs. Go beyond monitoring assets and catch potential issues before they turn into problems. View predictive maintenance analytics using the dashboard.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Try the demo&#xA;Provision the service&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/InternetOfThings/IoTSolutionAccelerator.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="70x40"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
