<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="MicrosoftGenomics"
    id="9682a79b-1638-40bf-adfb-050ddc4db31c"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/genomics/&#xA;&#xA;Microsoft Genomics&#xA;Power genome sequencing and research insights&#xA;&#xA;Cloud implementation of Burrows-Wheeler Aligner (BWA) and the Genome Analysis Toolkit (GATK) for secondary analysis&#xA;ISO-certified and covered by Microsoft under the HIPAA BAA&#xA;Global coverage to meet your data sovereignty needs&#xA;Only pay for what you use with no commitment&#xA;Easy-to-use API for integration with partner solutions&#xA;&#xA;Support your most demanding sequencing needs&#xA;Instead of managing your own datacenters, take advantage of Microsoft's scale and experience in running exabyte-scale workloads. Because Microsoft Genomics is on Azure, you have the performance and scalability of a world-class supercomputing center, on demand in the cloud. Take advantage of a backend network with MPI latency under three microseconds and non-blocking 32 gigabits per second (Gbps) throughput. This backend network includes remote direct memory access (RDMA) technology that enables parallel applications to scale to thousands of cores. Azure provides you with high memory and HPC-class CPUs to help you get results fast. Scale up and down based upon what you need and pay only for what you use to reduce costs.&#xA;&#xA;Meet industry-specific compliance standards&#xA;Tackle data sovereignty requirements with a worldwide network of Azure datacenters and adhere to your compliance requirements—Microsoft Genomics is ISO 27001, ISO 27018, and ISO 9001 certified and covered by Microsoft under the HIPAA Business Associate Agreement (BAA).&#xA;&#xA;Work with your existing tools&#xA;Easily integrate into your existing pipeline code using a REST-based API and simple python client, or take advantage of a growing ecosystem of solution partners who’ve already integrated with Microsoft Genomics.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Bring price predictability to your sequencing projects&#xA;Pay as you go with no upfront commitment. Ensure price predictability using a simple per-genome billing model that’s based on the number of gigabases in your samples. And, a single experience for billing and support keeps your project on track and within budget.&#xA;&#xA;Draw on Microsoft Research innovation&#xA;Take advantage of a service that not only applies a decade of genome analysis research, but provides constant updates to make computational innovations based on research investments available to you immediately.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Related products and services&#xA;Batch&#xA;Cloud-scale job scheduling and compute management&#xA;&#xA;Azure ExpressRoute&#xA;Dedicated private network fiber connections to Azure&#xA;&#xA;Blob storage&#xA;REST-based object storage for unstructured data&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;&#xA;Microsoft computing method makes key aspect of genomic sequencing seven times faster&#xA;A Practical Guide to Designing Secure Health Solutions using Microsoft Azure&#xA;Genomics: Partnering to Advance Clinical Genomics&#xA;Resources&#xA;&#xA;DNAnexus launches platform on Azure&#xA;Codigo, BC Platforms, Microsoft partner for genomic data solutions">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/MicrosoftGenomics.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
