<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzurePipelines"
    id="633bd4f4-9a2e-4a63-9498-6953a416c9f6"
    documentation="Build, test, and deploy in any language, to any cloud—or on-premises. Run in parallel on Linux, macOS, and Windows, and deploy containers to individual hosts or Kubernetes.&#xA;&#xA;Get cloud-hosted pipelines for Linux, macOS, and Windows. build web, desktop and mobile applications. Deploy to any cloud or on‑premises.&#xA;Automate your builds and deployments with Pipelines so you spend less time with the nuts and bolts and more time being creative.&#xA;&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/devops/pipelines/&#xA;&#xA;Any language, any platform&#xA;Build, test, and deploy Node.js, Python, Java, PHP, Ruby, C/C++, .NET, Android, and iOS apps. Run in parallel on Linux, macOS, and Windows.&#xA;Containers and Kubernetes&#xA;Easily build and push images to container registries like Docker Hub and Azure Container Registry. Deploy containers to individual hosts or Kubernetes.&#xA;Extensible&#xA;Explore and implement a wide range of community-built build, test, and deployment tasks, along with hundreds of extensions from Slack to SonarCloud.&#xA;Deploy to any cloud&#xA;Implement continuous delivery (CD) of your software to any cloud, including Azure, AWS, and GCP. Visualize deployment to any number of interdependent stages.&#xA;Free for open source&#xA;Ensure fast continuous integration/continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipelines for every open source project. Get 10 free parallel jobs with unlimited build minutes for all open source projects.&#xA;Advanced workflows and features&#xA;Take advantage of easy build chaining and multi-phased builds. Support for YAML, test integration, release gates, reporting—and more.&#xA;&#xA;GitHub user? You’re covered.&#xA;Build, test, and deploy everything you create on GitHub. Get fast, reliable builds on all platforms through deep integration with GitHub pull requests, checks, and statuses.&#xA;&#xA;Linux, macOS, and Windows agents—hosted by Microsoft&#xA;Simplify managing hardware and VMs by using Microsoft cloud-hosted agents. Get full CI/CD pipeline support for every major platform and tool.&#xA;&#xA;Powerful workflows with native container support&#xA;Get lightning fast builds with parallel jobs and test execution. Use container jobs to create consistent and reliable builds with the exact tools you need. Create new containers with ease and push them to any registry.&#xA;&#xA;Flexible deployments to Kubernetes, serverless, or VMs&#xA;Deploy to Kubernetes, VMs, Azure Functions, Azure Web Apps, or any cloud. Use stages, gates, and approvals to create a deployment strategy that’s right for you and ensures quality at every step. Even deploy from other CI systems, like Jenkins.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/DevOps/AzurePipelines.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
