<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureContainerRegistry"
    id="76bfb9af-6e82-4f02-8b95-56e964bfd4fc"
    documentation="A registry of Docker and Open Container Initiative (OCI) images, with support for all OCI artifacts&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/container-registry/&#xA;&#xA;Build, store, secure, scan, replicate, and manage container images and artifacts with a fully managed, geo-replicated instance of OCI distribution. Connect across environments, including Azure Kubernetes Service and Azure Red Hat OpenShift, and across Azure services like App Service, Machine Learning, and Batch.&#xA;&#xA;Geo-replication to efficiently manage a single registry across multiple regions&#xA;&#xA;OCI artifact repository for adding Helm charts, Singularity support, and new OCI artifact-supported formats&#xA;&#xA;Automated container building and patching including base image updates and task scheduling&#xA;&#xA;Integrated security with Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) authentication, role-based access control, Docker Content Trust, and virtual network integration&#xA;&#xA;Store your container images and beyond: Enable fast, scalable retrieval of container workloads. Azure Container Registry handles private Docker container images as well as related content formats, such as Helm charts, OCI artifacts, and images built to the OCI image format specification.&#xA;&#xA;Utilize pipelines for development and patching: Streamline building, testing, pushing, and deploying images to Azure with Azure Container Registry Tasks. For example, extend your development inner-loop to the cloud by offloading docker build operations to Azure with az acr build. Configure tasks to automatically rebuild application images when base images are updated, or automate image builds when your team commits code to a Git repository. Create multi-step tasks to automate building, testing, and patching multiple container images in parallel, in the cloud. Automate time-based tasks with Task Scheduling.&#xA;&#xA;Scale globally with a few clicks: Enable a single registry to serve users and hosts wherever they are, with multi-master geo-replication. Synchronize an artifact across all replicas by pushing it to any one replica. Speed up deployment by using regionalized webhooks to receive notifications when a local pull becomes available.&#xA;&#xA;Put private images on a private network: Get both the security of a private network and the robustness of a managed, geo-replicated service, using Azure Virtual Network integration and firewall rules. Restrict access to your registry to services deployed within a virtual network—for example, to an Azure Kubernetes Service instance.&#xA;&#xA;Help safeguard content delivery with Content Trust: Ensure the content you pull from the registry is the content run on the node. Sign container images you push to the registry and configure image consumers to verify image integrity upon pulling.&#xA;&#xA;Check images with Azure Security Center integration (Preview): Scan all images pushed to Azure Container Registry. Discover any known vulnerabilities in packages or other dependencies defined in the container image file. Receive vulnerability assessments and recommendations, including specific remediation guidance.&#xA;&#xA;Tutoriel at https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/container-instances/container-instances-tutorial-prepare-app&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Containers/AzureContainerRegistry.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
