<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureExpressRoute"
    id="c3b40233-a1e1-4b50-8a81-52b273d5ae5a"
    documentation="Azure ExpressRoute&#xA;Experience a faster, private connection to Azure&#xA;&#xA;Private connections to Azure&#xA;Increased reliability and speed&#xA;Lower latency&#xA;Bandwidth up to 100 Gbps Supported&#xA;Connects directly to your WAN&#xA;Connect your on-premises networks using the Microsoft global network&#xA;&#xA;Make your connections fast, reliable, and private&#xA;&#xA;Use Azure ExpressRoute to create private connections between Azure datacenters and infrastructure on your premises or in a colocation environment. ExpressRoute connections don't go over the public Internet, and they offer more reliability, faster speeds, and lower latencies than typical Internet connections. In some cases, using ExpressRoute connections to transfer data between on-premises systems and Azure can give you significant cost benefits.&#xA;&#xA;With ExpressRoute, establish connections to Azure at an ExpressRoute location, such as an Exchange provider facility, or directly connect to Azure from your existing WAN network, such as a multiprotocol label switching (MPLS) VPN, provided by a network service provider.&#xA;&#xA;Use a virtual private cloud for storage, backup, and recovery&#xA;&#xA;ExpressRoute gives you a fast and reliable connection to Azure with bandwidths up to 100 Gbps, which makes it excellent for scenarios like periodic data migration, replication for business continuity, disaster recovery, and other high-availability strategies. It can be a cost-effective option for transferring large amounts of data, such as datasets for high-performance computing applications, or moving large virtual machines between your dev-test environment in an Azure virtual private cloud and your on-premises production environments.&#xA;Extend and connect your datacenters&#xA;&#xA;Use ExpressRoute to both connect and add compute and storage capacity to your existing datacenters. With high throughput and fast latencies, Azure will feel like a natural extension to or between your datacenters, so you enjoy the scale and economics of the public cloud without having to compromise on network performance.&#xA;Build hybrid applications&#xA;&#xA;With predictable, reliable, and high-throughput connections offered by ExpressRoute, build applications that span on-premises infrastructure and Azure without compromising privacy or performance. For example, run a corporate intranet application in Azure that authenticates your customers with an on-premises Active Directory service, and serve all of your corporate customers without traffic ever routing through the public Internet.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Networking/AzureExpressRoute.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
