<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureSqlStretchDatabase"
    id="41a43744-6d2a-4c2d-96d6-8ae256dd7639"
    documentation="SQL Server Stretch Database&#xA;Dynamically stretch on-premises SQL Server databases to Azure&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/sql-server-stretch-database/&#xA;Scale SQL Server 2016 using the cloud storage you need&#xA;Make warm and cold data available to customers at low cost&#xA;Access and query stretched data online&#xA;Move data easily—no query or application changes required&#xA;Use with advanced security features like Always Encrypted&#xA;Reduce maintenance and storage costs for on-premises data&#xA;&#xA;Make warm and cold data available at a low cost&#xA;SQL Server Stretch Database lets you dynamically stretch warm and cold transactional data from Microsoft SQL Server 2016 to Microsoft Azure. Unlike typical cold data storage, your data is always at hand. With Stretch Database, you can provide longer data retention times without breaking the bank. Rather than scaling expensive, on-premises storage, stretch data to the cloud—Azure storage can be up to 40 percent less expensive than adding more enterprise storage. Depending on how often you’ll access the data, choose the appropriate transaction level, and then scale up or down as needed. To learn more, see SQL Server Stretch Database pricing.&#xA;Move data without query or application changes&#xA;Access SQL Server data if it’s on-premises or stretched to the cloud. You set policy that determines where data is stored and SQL Server moves the data in the background for you. The table is online and ready to query, and you don’t have to change existing queries or applications—it’s completely transparent.&#xA;Use advanced security options&#xA;With Stretch Database, use SQL Server Always Encrypted to encrypt your data in motion. Row-Level Security and other advanced SQL Server security features also work with Stretch Database, enabling you to extend data to the cloud with greater peace of mind.&#xA;Streamline on-premises data maintenance&#xA;Reduce on-premises maintenance times and your storage footprint by moving data to Azure. With Stretch Database, backups for your on-premises data run faster and complete more easily than they did on the un-stretched data. Backup is automatic for stretched data, further reducing the amount of time you spend on maintenance.&#xA;Manage easily&#xA;Turn on Stretch Database from SQL Server Management Studio. Use the Azure portal to configure additional settings and choose a performance level, scaling up or down as needed while keeping control over cost.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Databases/AzureSqlStretchDatabase.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
