<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureCosmosDb"
    id="41626e53-8845-4f66-ad81-70d6dbaa874f"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/cosmos-db/&#xA;Azure Cosmos DB&#xA;Fast NoSQL database with open APIs for any scale&#xA;Build or modernize scalable, high-performance apps&#xA;Azure Cosmos DB is a fully managed NoSQL database service for modern app development with guaranteed single-digit millisecond response times and 99.999-percent availability backed by SLAs, automatic and instant scalability, and open source APIs for MongoDB and Cassandra. Enjoy fast writes and reads anywhere in the world with turnkey multi-master global distribution.&#xA;&#xA;New accounts get 400 RU/s throughput and 5 GBs storage free each month&#xA;Guaranteed speed at any scale – even through bursts - with instant limitless elasticity, fast reads and multi-master writes anywhere in the world&#xA;&#xA;Fast, flexible app development with SDKs for popular languages, APIs for SQL, MongoDB, Cassandra and more, and no-ETL analytics&#xA;&#xA;Ready for mission-critical applications with guaranteed business continuity, 99.999-percent availability, and enterprise-level security&#xA;&#xA;Fully managed and cost-effective serverless database with instant, automatic scaling that responds to application needs&#xA;&#xA;Mission-critical applications&#xA;Run your most critical workloads in any Azure region in the world with SLA-backed speed, availability, throughput, and consistency. Ensure business continuity with turnkey multi-master replication and enterprise-grade security and compliance including end-to-end encryption and access control. Azure Cosmos DB is trusted by leading enterprises globally including Coca-Cola, Symantec, and Citrix.&#xA;&#xA;Mission-critical applications&#xA;No-ETL analytics over real-time operational data&#xA;Run near-real time analytics and AI on the operational data within your database, to reduce time to insight. Azure Cosmos DB seamlessly integrates with Azure Synapse Analytics without data movement or diminishing the performance of your operational store.&#xA;&#xA;No-ETL analytics over real-time operational dataPause gifPlaying gif&#xA;Real-time IoT device telemetry&#xA;Scale instantly and elastically to accommodate diverse and unpredictable IoT workloads without sacrificing ingestion or query performance. Stream vehicle telemetry for smart fleet solutions, stream and analyze data with Change Feed for real-time insights, or archive data for data warehouse analytics. ExxonMobil, Johnson Controls, and Olympus are among the market leaders who rely on Azure Cosmos DB to power IoT solutions.&#xA;&#xA;Real-time IoT device telemetry&#xA;Real-time retail services&#xA;Deliver high-performance digital customer experiences with real-time shopping cart, product recommendations, dynamic pricing, inventory updates, and more. Used by leading retailers including Jet.com and ASOS, Azure Cosmos DB enables fast and global personalization across high volumes of product data, analyzed in milliseconds, while low-latency database response times ensure superior app performance anywhere in the world.&#xA;&#xA;Real-time retail services&#xA;Develop apps with Azure Cosmos DB solution architectures&#xA;Design and implement breakthrough IoT, e-commerce, gaming, and serverless applications with data distribution across any number of Azure regions.&#xA;&#xA;Explore solution architectures">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Databases/AzureCosmosDb.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
