<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureIotHub"
    id="faf9b690-1d06-4f7e-8c12-feb6a7a580ff"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/iot-hub/&#xA;Azure IoT Hub&#xA;Connect, monitor and manage billions of IoT assets`&#xA;Build your IoT application with two-way communication&#xA;Enable highly secure and reliable communication between your IoT application and the devices it manages. Azure IoT Hub provides a cloud-hosted solution backend to connect virtually any device. Extend your solution from the cloud to the edge with per-device authentication, built-in device management, and scaled provisioning.&#xA;Security-enhanced communication channel for sending and receiving data from IoT devices&#xA;Built-in device management and provisioning to connect and manage IoT devices at scale&#xA;Full integration with Event Grid and serverless compute, simplifying IoT application development&#xA;Compatibility with Azure IoT Edge for building hybrid IoT applications&#xA;&#xA;Establish bidirectional communication with billions of IoT devices&#xA;&#xA;Use device-to-cloud telemetry data to understand the state of your devices and define message routes to other Azure services—without writing any code. In cloud-to-device messages, reliably send commands and notifications to your connected devices and track message delivery with acknowledgement receipts. Automatically resend device messages as needed to accommodate intermittent connectivity.&#xA;&#xA;Read the documentation&#xA;Authenticate every device for enhanced security&#xA;&#xA;Set up individual identities and credentials for each of your connected devices to help retain the confidentiality of both cloud-to-device and device-to-cloud messages. Selectively revoke access rights for specific devices as needed.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about Azure security for IoT&#xA;Automate device provisioning to accelerate IoT deployment&#xA;&#xA;Register and provision devices with zero touches, in a highly secure and scalable way. IoT Hub Device Provisioning Service supports any type of IoT device compatible with IoT Hub.&#xA;&#xA;Read about IoT Hub device provisioning&#xA;Extend the power of the cloud to your edge devices&#xA;&#xA;Easily create and deploy IoT Edge modules to transmit code and services between the cloud and the edge. Distribute intelligence—including AI and other advanced analytics—across a range of devices. All while reducing your IoT application costs, easing development efforts, and running devices offline or with intermittent connectivity.&#xA;&#xA;Explore IoT Edge&#xA;Comprehensive security and compliance, built in the largest compliance portfolio in the industry&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Reduce risk by using security posture management and threat monitoring and remediation, with Azure Security Center for IoT.&#xA;Increase connection security by connecting IoT devices to IoT Hub via virtual networks.&#xA;Join startups, governments, and 95 percent of the Fortune 500 putting their trust in the Microsoft Cloud.&#xA;Help protect your business assets with our stringent security standards and the largest portfolio of compliance certifications in the industry.&#xA;Learn more about security on Azure&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/InternetOfThings/AzureIoTHub.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
