<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="VisualStudiCodeSpace"
    id="618ad74f-92c1-4fe9-8f2d-c213be7617ac"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/visual-studio-online/&#xA;&#xA;Create and manage development environments in the cloud&#xA;Be ready to code in minutes, with cloud-powered development environments that can be used for day-to-day development or short-term tasks like pull requests. Create as many environments as you need and connect to them with the IDE of your choice, including Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio (support in private preview), or the included browser-based editor.&#xA;Edit and collaborate more productively using breakpoint debugging, AI-powered completions, and real-time co-editing features&#xA;Choose environment sizes to match the amount of resources (including GPU resources) needed for each project or task, and temporarily scale up an environment for intensive tasks&#xA;Use the programming languages and frameworks of your choice, including Node.js, Python, and .NET Core&#xA;Avoid wasting unused resources—environments don’t have time limits, and they suspend when you’re not using them&#xA;Onboard new projects quickly&#xA;&#xA;Get to code quickly by providing a fully configured development environment in minutes. When you include a reference to a code repository, Visual Studio Codespaces automatically sets up the source code, runtime, tools, and extensions.&#xA;Learn how to create an environment&#xA;How to prepare an environment in VS Code Pause gif Playing gif&#xA;Develop from anywhere&#xA;&#xA;Seamlessly roam across machines or IDEs while working on the same environment, without needing to reconfigure settings. If you need to access an environment that doesn’t have an IDE installed, connect using the built-in browser-based editor and pick up right where you left off.&#xA;Easily connect to other services&#xA;&#xA;Add extensions to your environments from the Visual Studio Marketplace to get additional languages and debuggers, and to connect to other services. Using the built-in support for Git and other source control providers, set up continuous integration or automation workflows by connecting your repository to GitHub Actions or Azure Pipelines and deploy to the platform, cloud, or server of your choice.&#xA;Read the documentation"/>
