<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDatabricks"
    id="2aa3f7c1-faf4-46b6-9fef-8697d37b7e7c"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/databricks/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Databricks&#xA;Fast, easy, and collaborative Apache SparkTM based analytics service&#xA;&#xA;Big data analytics and AI with optimized Apache Spark&#xA;&#xA;Unlock insights from all your data and build artificial intelligence (AI) solutions with Azure Databricks, set up your Apache Spark™ environment in minutes, autoscale, and collaborate on shared projects in an interactive workspace. Azure Databricks supports Python, Scala, R, Java, and SQL, as well as data science frameworks and libraries including TensorFlow, PyTorch, and scikit-learn.&#xA;&#xA;Apache Spark™ is a trademark of the Apache Software Foundation.&#xA;Azure Databricks offers new capabilities at a lower cost –– Read the blog&#xA;Fast, optimized Apache Spark environment&#xA;Interactive workspace with built-in support for popular tools, languages, and frameworks&#xA;Supercharged machine learning on big data with native Azure Machine Learning integration&#xA;High-performance modern data warehousing in conjunction with Azure Synapse Analytics&#xA;&#xA;Start quickly with an optimized Apache Spark environment&#xA;&#xA;Azure Databricks provides the latest versions of Apache Spark and allows you to seamlessly integrate with open source libraries. Spin up clusters and build quickly in a fully managed Apache Spark environment with the global scale and availability of Azure. Clusters are set up, configured, and fine-tuned to ensure reliability and performance without the need for monitoring. Take advantage of autoscaling and auto-termination to improve total cost of ownership (TCO).&#xA;&#xA;Read Azure Databricks documentation&#xA;&#xA;Boost productivity with a shared workspace and common languages&#xA;&#xA;Collaborate effectively on shared projects using the interactive workspace and notebook experience, whether you’re a data engineer, data scientist, or business analyst. Build with your choice of language, including Python, Scala, R, and SQL. Get easy version control of notebooks with GitHub and Azure DevOps.&#xA;&#xA;Learn how to create an Azure Databricks workspace&#xA;&#xA;Turbocharge machine learning on big data&#xA;&#xA;Access advanced automated machine learning capabilities using the integrated Azure Machine Learning to quickly identify suitable algorithms and hyperparameters. Simplify management, monitoring, and updating of machine learning models deployed from the cloud to the edge. Azure Machine Learning also provides a central registry for your experiments, machine learning pipelines, and models.&#xA;&#xA;Watch a webinar on Azure Databricks and Azure Machine Learning&#xA;&#xA;Get high-performance modern data warehousing&#xA;&#xA;Modernize your data warehouse in the cloud for unmatched levels of performance and scalability. Combine data at any scale, and get insights through analytical dashboards and operational reports. Automate data movement using Azure Data Factory, load data into Azure Data Lake Storage, transform and clean it using Azure Databricks, and then make it available for analytics using Azure Synapse Analytics.&#xA;&#xA;Learn about modern data warehousing on Azure&#xA;Industry-leading security and compliance&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Take advantage of native integration with Azure Active Directory for role-based access control.&#xA;Create secure architectures without compromising on compliance using configurable virtual networks.&#xA;Get peace of mind with fine-grained user permissions for Azure Databricks notebooks, clusters, jobs, and data.&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Analytics/AzureDatabricks.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
