<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureSphere"
    id="23d14cbd-4e01-4185-870c-6421464e0909"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/azure-sphere/&#xA;Azure Sphere&#xA;Comprehensive IoT security solution—including hardware, OS, and cloud components—to actively protect your devices, your business, and your customers&#xA;&#xA;Unlock the value of IoT with confidence in your security&#xA;With billions of new devices connected each year, it’s more important than ever to secure yours. Help protect your data, privacy, physical safety, and infrastructure with Azure Sphere. It’s built on decades of Microsoft experience in hardware, software, and cloud to provide a turnkey security solution for IoT devices.&#xA;&#xA;Unlock the value of IoT with confidence in your security&#xA;With billions of new devices connected each year, it’s more important than ever to secure yours. Help protect your data, privacy, physical safety, and infrastructure with Azure Sphere. It’s built on decades of Microsoft experience in hardware, software, and cloud to provide a turnkey security solution for IoT devices.&#xA;&#xA;Azure Sphere is now generally available. Read more&#xA;Defense in depth provides multiple layers of protection to help guard devices against and respond to threats&#xA;&#xA;Deployment flexibility helps you secure existing equipment and build protection into new IoT investments&#xA;&#xA;Over-the-air (OTA) updates make it easy to add new features and improve performance throughout device lifecycles&#xA;&#xA;Error reporting and automatic security updates help you stay ahead of new and evolving threats&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Protect your IoT devices and equipment with defense in depth&#xA;Azure Sphere–certified chips from hardware partners include built-in Microsoft security technology to provide connectivity and a dependable hardware root of trust.&#xA;Azure Sphere OS adds layers of protection and ongoing security updates to create a trustworthy platform for new IoT experiences.&#xA;Azure Sphere Security Service brokers trust for device-to-cloud communication, detects threats, and renews device security.&#xA;Microsoft best-in-class security experts monitor emerging threats, design updates, and provide a decade of ongoing servicing.&#xA;Deliver new experiences that help keep customers safe&#xA;Companies are taking their industries forward in new ways, realizing that investing in security is critical to effectively serving and protecting their customers. Learn how GOJO, LEONI, Grundfos, and qiio are delivering secure IoT solutions.&#xA;&#xA;Maximize the value of equipment that’s already in place&#xA;Bring the benefits of connectivity to legacy equipment that’s already in service—brownfield equipment—without exposing it to the internet. With an Azure Sphere guardian module, IoT retrofits are more secure, substantially easier, and more cost-effective than ever.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;&#xA;Build new IoT devices that stay highly secured&#xA;With Azure Sphere, manufacturers and solution providers can build devices that are secure from the start and that stay secure throughout the device lifetime. Give your customers differentiated value and peace of mind while growing your business. Research by Greenberg Strategy shows that security can help drive market share.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/InternetOfThings/Sphere.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
