<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureMediaPlayer"
    id="8c0d18f9-72e4-43df-8729-e5c41621224c"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/media-services/media-player/&#xA;Azure Media Player&#xA;Your content. Multiple devices. One player.&#xA;Supports most popular screens and devices&#xA;Automatically chooses the best playback format&#xA;Easily integrates into web and app solutions&#xA;Lets you use familiar JavaScript API development&#xA;Includes automatic fallback for Flash and Silverlight&#xA;Gives you integrated content protection&#xA;Automatic playback on the most popular devices&#xA;Azure Media Player automatically picks the best format for a browser or device, and uses the dynamic packaging capabilities of Azure Media Services to play adaptive streaming content in formats like MPEG-DASH, Microsoft Smooth Streaming, or Apple HTTP Live Streaming (HLS). Media Player is also designed to select the correct technology based on the platform—HTML5 (MSE/EME), Adobe Flash Player, or Microsoft Silverlight.&#xA;&#xA;Develop faster and more simply&#xA;Regardless of the playback technology, there’s a simple interface to access APIs. Media Player gives you simplified development using standard HTML5 video tags. A unified JavaScript interface lets advanced customers create a media player experience without having to develop for specific platforms or features.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about Azure Media Player&#xA;&#xA;Deliver your content securely&#xA;Media Player supports content secured with DRM technology, through Microsoft PlayReady and Widevine, or Advanced Encryption Standard (AES) 128-bit clear-key encryption.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;&#xA;Reach a global audience with an accessible player&#xA;Reach audiences around the world with the ability to playback multi-language audio streams, see subtitles, and localize the player. Provide equal access and opportunity for all of your customers through accessibility features for seeing captions with fonts they can customize, interaction with screen readers, and controls through touch, mouse, and keyboard.&#xA;&#xA;Easier debugging&#xA;Use the Azure Media Player Diagnostics Center to debug player issues and monitor the quality of your adaptive bitrate media streams. It shows you diagnostic player information and you can download logs for more debugging.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Media/AzureMediaPlayer.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
