<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureBotService"
    id="67cc9b22-65de-41a3-9444-544615b551b2"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/bot-service/&#xA;Intelligent, serverless bot service that scales on demand&#xA;&#xA;Build conversational experiences for your customers&#xA;&#xA;Develop intelligent, enterprise-grade bots that help you enrich the customer experience while maintaining control of your data. Build any type of bot—from a Q&amp;A bot to your own branded virtual assistant—to quickly connect your users to the answers they need.&#xA;Create a bot that can naturally interact with users by easily integrating Cognitive Services&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Use open-source SDK and tools to build, test, and publish your bot to Azure&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Deploy your bot to popular channels, wherever your customers interact&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Create your own branded virtual assistant using solution accelerators&#xA;&#xA;Easily add natural language and speech to your bot&#xA;Integrate powerful AI capabilities with Azure Cognitive Services to keep pace with technological advances without machine learning experience. Improve experiences by giving your users the ability to interact with your bot using natural language and speech capabilities.&#xA;&#xA;Start simply and grow in sophistication&#xA;Build with an open and extensible bot framework that enables you to build a basic informational bot to alleviate the high volume of common inquiries from your users. Then, as your scenarios become more nuanced, create more advanced bots, including virtual assistants that can handle rich, multiturn conversations that make it easier to engage with your users.&#xA;&#xA;Reach your customers, wherever they interact&#xA;Integrate Bot Service across multiple communication channels to reach more customers, more often. Apply bots to channels including your website or apps, Microsoft Teams, Skype, Slack, Cortana, and Facebook Messenger.&#xA;&#xA;Your assistant, your brand, your data&#xA;Deliver personalized experiences to customers without compromising ownership and control of customer data. Deploy a virtual assistant tailored to your brand, across multiple apps and devices, with the Virtual Assistant solution accelerator.&#xA;Extend your bots with skills&#xA;Whether you’re starting with Bot Service or Power Virtual Agents, extend your bot with an open-source bot framework SDK and collaborate with business users to bring their ideas to life.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Seamlessly transition conversations with customers from bot to human agent&#xA;Create a sophisticated bot to identify when to bring in a human agent. For common scenarios including customer escalations and help desk triage, your bot can interpret customer sentiment and intent with Azure Cognitive Services such as Text Analytics and Language Understanding.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/AIMachineLearning/AzureBotService.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
