<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureBatch"
    id="9f10916e-e8d2-4312-95c4-d0b2b7df3e8a"
    documentation="Batch pricing GA&#xA;Cloud-scale job scheduling and compute management&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/details/batch/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Batch provides job scheduling and cluster management, allowing applications or algorithms to run in parallel at scale.&#xA;&#xA;There’s no charge for Batch itself, only the underlying compute and other resources consumed to run your batch jobs, including applicable software license costs. For compute, Cloud Services, Linux Virtual Machines, or Windows Virtual Machines can be utilized by Batch. The standard rates for compute apply and can be viewed below; software licensing costs for batch graphics and rendering are available below.&#xA;&#xA;Low-priority VMs&#xA;Low-priority VMs can significantly reduce the costs of running certain workloads or allow much more work to be performed at a greater scale for the same cost. However, these VMs do have different characteristics and are only suitable for certain types of applications and workloads. The VMs are allocated from surplus capacity and therefore availability varies—at times, VMs may not be available to allocate, and allocated VMs may be preempted. The availability SLA for pay-as-you-go VMs therefore does not apply to spot and low-priority VMs.&#xA;&#xA;If applications can tolerate interruption, then use of low-priority VMs can significantly lower compute costs. Suitable workloads include batch processing and HPC jobs, where the work is split into many asynchronous tasks. If VMs are pre-empted, then tasks can be interrupted and rerun—job completion time can also increase if capacity drops. Azure Batch pools can contain both normal and low-priority VMs. If low-priority VMs are pre-empted, then any interrupted tasks will be requeued, and the pool will automatically attempt to replace the lost capacity.&#xA;&#xA;Pricing for low-priority VMs is displayed below. For spot VM pricing, see the pricing page for Virtual Machine Scale Sets.&#xA;&#xA;Virtual machines are billed per-second rounded down to the last minute.&#xA;&#xA;Note: Azure Batch will add support for Spot VMs once Spot VMs is GA, with new versions of the Batch APIs and tools being made available. When support for Spot VMs is added, low-priority VMs will be deprecated, but it will be possible to use them for at least a year using the existing API and tool versions.&#xA;&#xA;Av2 Standard *&#xA;Av2 Standard is the latest generation of A-series virtual machines with similar CPU performance and faster disk. These virtual machines are suitable for development workloads, build servers, code repositories, low-traffic websites and web applications, micro services, early product experiments, and small databases. Like the prior A Standard generation, Av2 virtual machines will include load balancing and auto-scaling at no additional charge.&#xA;&#xA;D2a – D96a v4&#xA;The Da v4-series VMs are based on the 2.35Ghz AMD EPYCTM 7452 processor, which can achieve up to 3.35GHz. The Dav4 VM sizes offer a combination of vCPU(s), memory and temporary storage able to meet the requirements associated with most production workloads. Data disk storage is billed separately from virtual machines. To use Premium SSD disk storage, select the Das v4 VMs.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Compute/AzureBatch.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
