<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Visual Studio"
    id="db12b8cf-4042-4ee9-b5a4-9d4c213c89c6"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/products/visual-studio/&#xA;Visual Studio&#xA;The integrated development environment (IDE) designed for creating powerful, scalable applications for Azure&#xA;&#xA;The IDE designed for cloud solutions&#xA;Develop, debug, and monitor cloud applications locally, and deploy to production using powerful integration tools. Use the range of features and capabilities to quickly and efficiently create highly secure applications optimized for the cloud.&#xA;Learn new monitoring skills, get Azure Monitor updates, and ask questions at this free, online event on April 28. Register now&#xA;Local emulators and integration tools to build, run, and debug cloud apps directly from the integrated development environment (IDE)&#xA;Azure Monitor integration to automatically detect performance anomalies and gain insights into users’ behaviors&#xA;Built-in Cloud Explorer to help enhance productivity and reduce context switching&#xA;Snapshot debugging to easily identify and fix unhandled exceptions that occur in production&#xA;Azure Functions with Storage Emulator Playing&#xA;Develop cloud applications locally&#xA;&#xA;Work with your cloud apps locally, without the need to sign into Azure. Just install Azure Storage, CosmosDB, SQL, or Azure Functions emulators, tools, or runtimes. Radically simplify running and debugging serverless application with Azure Functions by responding to events in production, in real time. When your applications are ready to deploy, easily target them to the cloud without leaving the IDE.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;App Insights and CodeLens Playing&#xA;Drive insightful monitoring and diagnostics&#xA;&#xA;More easily find and solve performance issues and bugs in production. Azure Monitor (formerly Application Insights) within Visual Studio helps you identify dependency failures and troubleshoot slow performance with actionable suggestions directly inside your IDE using CodeLens hints.&#xA;&#xA;Get details&#xA;Snapshot debugger Playing&#xA;Easily fix issues in production&#xA;&#xA;Quickly respond to bugs and issues in production while building robust applications. With Snapshot Debugger, find and fix unhandled exceptions and replicate the steps that caused the code failure, using the same live data, without the need for debug symbols or additional instrumentation. Simply grab the latest debug snapshot from Application Insights, and use the Snapshot Debugger to fix the problematic code with precision.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;IntelliTrace debugging Playing&#xA;Debug after deployment using built-in tools&#xA;&#xA;Easily find and resolve bugs and performance issues in your cloud apps, using Snapshot Debugger and other powerful tools. Switch on IntelliTrace to track and record your code’s execution history, whether your application is running locally or in Azure. Step through the code execution and replay actions using Travel Debugging.&#xA;Explore IntelliTrace&#xA;Publish to Azure App Service Playing&#xA;Quickly publish and test on Azure&#xA;&#xA;Whether you’re building a web app or a web job, a complex workflow orchestrator with Azure Logic Apps, or a serverless solution with Azure Functions, deploy your code directly from Visual Studio to Azure using the powerful, integrated Cloud Explorer and Publish Wizard. Select the right Azure subscription, create resources, deploy databases, and push your code to the cloud in only a few steps.&#xA;Learn about Cloud Explorer&#xA;Creating a pull request in Visual Studio Playing&#xA;Reimagine developer productivity&#xA;&#xA;Innovate at scale and enrich your enterprise projects by tapping open-source code, community, and best practices available on GitHub. Create and publish repos, manage pull requests on GitHub, and review source code right inside Visual Studio. Purchase Visual Studio and GitHub Enterprise together at one low price.&#xA;Download GitHub extension for Visual Studio">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/DeveloperTools/VisualStudio.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
