<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="SpatialAnchor"
    id="e908a7db-7eba-4931-853e-f4f30d33f2d6"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/spatial-anchors/&#xA;Spatial Anchors&#xA;Build apps that map, share, and persist 3D content&#xA;&#xA;Build cross-platform mixed reality applications with spatial context&#xA;More easily build rich immersive 3D applications and experiences that map, persist, and restore 3D content or points of interest at real-world scale.&#xA;Persist and Share 3D Content&#xA;&#xA;Accelerate mixed reality app development by eliminating the difficult task of creating and restoring persistent, accurate digital anchors&#xA;Operate at Real-world Scale&#xA;&#xA;Spatial Anchors has a proven ability to operate at global scale persisting and restoring millions of 3D objects&#xA;With the Security and Reliability of Azure&#xA;&#xA;Ensure that your 3D content is rendering safely and reliably by leveraging Azure, the world’s computer&#xA;&#xA;Contextually integrate IoT data&#xA;&#xA;Connect your digital business data to your real-world workflows in facility management, manufacturing, and retail. Put real-time data at the fingertips of your employees, enabling them to make better, faster, and more informed decisions.&#xA;&#xA;Create massive multiplayer games in the real world&#xA;&#xA;Bring the best of mobile gaming and mixed reality together. Spatial Anchors enables players to find nearby content, share and play mixed reality experiences in a real-world location, and persist games and puzzles for discovery on later days, weeks or months. Build experiences such as Minecraft Earth, holographic scavenger hunts, or digital escape room puzzles.&#xA;&#xA;Enable collaborative experiences across platforms&#xA;&#xA;Share mixed reality content on all the devices that work best for your solution, for scenarios like training and design review. Spatial Anchors supports HoloLens devices, ARKit-enabled iOS devices, and ARCore-enabled Android devices. Build your apps using Unity or your favorite native SDK for the devices you choose to support.&#xA;See how it works&#xA;Build multi-user, cross-platform apps. Create persistent spatial anchors in the real world and attach digital content to those anchors. Enable wayfinding. With Azure Spatial Anchors, you have all of these capabilities at your fingertips. Watch them come together in a common scenario—architecture design review.&#xA;Spatial Anchors design review&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/MixedReality/AzureSpatialAnchor.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
