<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureSynapseAnalytics"
    id="c570c873-b45a-40f7-8fe8-f0d407c73369"
    documentation="Azure Synapse Analytics&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/synapse-analytics/&#xA;Limitless analytics service with unmatched time to insight (formerly SQL Data Warehouse)&#xA;Azure Synapse is Azure SQL Data Warehouse evolved&#xA;Azure Synapse is a limitless analytics service that brings together enterprise data warehousing and Big Data analytics. It gives you the freedom to query data on your terms, using either serverless or provisioned resources—at scale. Azure Synapse brings these two worlds together with a unified experience to ingest, prepare, manage, and serve data for immediate BI and machine learning needs.&#xA;See the new features&#xA;&#xA;Play VideoPlay&#x9;&#xA;Current Time 0:00&#xA;Loaded: 0%Progress: 0%Seekbar Handle&#xA;/&#xA;Duration Time 8:14&#xA;SubtitlesMute&#xA;Fullscreen&#xA;New features now in public preview&#xA;Get started with the new Azure Synapse features, now available in public preview, including the announcement of Azure Synapse Link.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Analytics in Azure is simply unmatched&#xA;Insights for all at incredible value. Simply unmatched. Analytics in Azure is up to 14 times faster and costs 94 percent less than other cloud providers. Why go anywhere else?&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Limitless scale&#xA;Deliver insights from all your data, across data warehouses and big data analytics systems, with blazing speed&#xA;Powerful insights&#xA;Expand discovery of insights from all your data and apply machine learning models to all your intelligent apps&#xA;Unified experience&#xA;Significantly reduce project development time with a unified experience for developing end-to-end analytics solutions&#xA;Instant clarity&#xA;Gain instant clarity on your business by using the freshest data possible from your operational systems, in every moment, with Synapse Link&#xA;Unmatched security&#xA;Secure data with the most advanced security and privacy features in the market, such as column- and row-level security and dynamic data masking&#xA;&#xA;Experience limitless scale and query data on your terms&#xA;&#xA;Azure Synapse delivers insights from all your data, across data warehouses and big data analytics systems, with blazing speed. With Azure Synapse, data professionals can query both relational and non-relational data at petabyte-scale using the familiar SQL language. For mission-critical workloads, they can easily optimize the performance of all queries with intelligent workload management, workload isolation, and limitless concurrency.&#xA;&#xA;Discover powerful insights across your most important data&#xA;&#xA;With Azure Synapse, enabling BI and machine learning is a breeze. It is deeply integrated with Power BI and Azure Machine Learning to greatly expand discovery of insights from all your data and apply machine learning models to all your intelligent apps. Significantly reduce project development time for BI and machine learning projects with a limitless analytics service that enables you to seamlessly apply intelligence over all your most important data—from Dynamics 365, Office 365 to SaaS services that support Open Data Initiative—and easily share data with just a few clicks.&#xA;&#xA;Harness the power of a unified analytics experience&#xA;&#xA;Build end-to-end analytics solutions with a unified experience. The Azure Synapse studio provides a unified workspace for data prep, data management, data warehousing, big data, and AI tasks. Data engineers can use a code-free visual environment for managing data pipelines. Database administrators can automate query optimization. Data scientists can build proofs of concept in minutes. Business analysts can securely access datasets and use Power BI to build dashboards in minutes—all while using the same analytics service.&#xA;Gain instant clarity using the freshest operational data at all times Pause gif Playing gif&#xA;Gain instant clarity using the freshest operational data at all times&#xA;&#xA;Bring immediate, in-the-moment insights to your business with a simple, low cost, cloud-native HTAP implementation using Azure Synapse Link. With a single click, you can remove the barriers between Azure databases and Azure Synapse to get insights from your live operational data stores in near-real time. No complex ETL pipelines or additional database compute resources are required and you can run your analytics workloads on live data through Azure Synapse, without affecting your operational systems. Business analysts, data engineers, and data scientists can now use Azure Synapse to run near real-time business intelligence, analytics, and machine learning pipelines without impacting the performance of their transactional workloads on Azure Cosmos DB.&#xA;&#xA;Safeguard data with unmatched security and privacy&#xA;&#xA;Azure has the most advanced security and privacy features in the market. These features are built into the fabric of Azure Synapse, such as automated threat detection and always-on data encryption. And for fine-grained access control businesses can help ensure data stays safe and private using column-level security and native row-level security, as well as dynamic data masking to automatically protect sensitive data in real time.&#xA;Key Service Capabilities&#xA;Enterprise data warehousing&#xA;Build your data warehouse on the proven foundation of the industry’s top-performing SQL engine.&#xA;Deeply integrated Apache Spark and SQL engines&#xA;Enhance collaboration among data professionals working on advanced analytics solutions. Easily use T-SQL queries on both your data warehouse and embedded Spark engine.&#xA;Data lake exploration&#xA;Bring together relational and non-relational data, and easily query files in the data lake with the same service you use to build data warehousing solutions.&#xA;Streaming ingestion &amp; analytics&#xA;Perform real-time analytics on streaming data directly in your data warehouse.&#xA;Choice of language&#xA;Use your preferred language, including T-SQL, Python, Scala, Spark SQL, and .Net—whether you use serverless or provisioned compute resources.&#xA;Integrated AI and BI&#xA;Complete your end-to-end analytics solution with deep integration of Azure Machine Learning and Power BI.&#xA;Code-free data orchestration&#xA;Build ETL/ELT processes in a code-free visual environment to easily ingest data from more than 85 native connectors.&#xA;Industry-leading management and security&#xA;Use built-in features to ensure your data and processes are seen by only those with authorized access.&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Analytics/Azure-Synapse-Analytics-Logo.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
