<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureIotEdge"
    id="d4e9edf0-770c-4392-a804-40177f4609e6"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/iot-edge/&#xA;Azure IoT Edge&#xA;Cloud intelligence deployed locally on IoT edge devices&#xA;Start free&#xA;Azure IoT Edge&#xA;Product overview&#xA;Features&#xA;Security&#xA;Pricing&#xA;Get started&#xA;Documentation&#xA;FAQs&#xA;Free account &#xA;Build the intelligent edge&#xA;Azure IoT Edge is a fully managed service built on Azure IoT Hub. Deploy your cloud workloads—artificial intelligence, Azure and third-party services, or your own business logic—to run on Internet of Things (IoT) edge devices via standard containers. By moving certain workloads to the edge of the network, your devices spend less time communicating with the cloud, react more quickly to local changes, and operate reliably even in extended offline periods.&#xA;Azure IoT Edge - Customer testimonial video &#xA;Certified IoT Edge hardware: Works with your Linux or Windows devices that support container engines&#xA;Runtime: Free and open-source under the MIT license to give you more control and code flexibility&#xA;Modules: Docker-compatible containers from Azure services or Microsoft partners to run your business logic at the edge&#xA;Cloud interface: Remotely manage and deploy workloads from the cloud through Azure IoT Hub with zero-touch device provisioning&#xA;Offload AI and analytics workloads to the edge&#xA;&#xA;Deploy models built and trained in the cloud and run them on-premises. For example, if you deploy a predictive model to a factory camera to test for quality control and an issue is detected, IoT Edge triggers an alert and processes the data locally or sends it to the cloud for further analysis.&#xA;&#xA;Watch Custom Vision AI on IoT Edge&#xA;&#xA;Order the Vision AI developer kit&#xA;Smart camera for Intelligent Edge &#xA;Simplify development&#xA;&#xA;Use existing developer skillsets and code in a language you know. IoT Edge code is consistent across the cloud and the edge, and it supports languages such as C, C#, Java, Node.js, and Python.&#xA;&#xA;Watch Getting Started with IoT Edge Development&#xA;&#xA;Learn how to prepare your development and test environment&#xA;Respond in near-real time&#xA;&#xA;Having the lowest latency possible between the data and the decision is critical. Rather than process your data in the cloud, IoT Edge processes it on the device itself, with the option of using hardware architecture from Microsoft called Project Brainwave. It uses a field-programmable gate array (FPGA) to make real-time AI calculations, giving you the immediate insights you need to make critical business decisions.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about Project Brainwave&#xA;Reduce IoT solution costs&#xA;&#xA;Only a small fraction of IoT edge data acquired is meaningful post-analytics. Use services such as Azure Stream Analytics or cloud-trained machine learning models to process the data locally and send only what’s needed to the cloud for further analysis. This reduces the cost associated with sending all your data to the cloud while maintaining high data quality.&#xA;&#xA;Get started with Azure Stream Analytics on IoT Edge&#xA;Operate offline or with intermittent connectivity&#xA;&#xA;Operate your edge devices reliably and securely, even when they’re offline or they have intermittent connectivity to the cloud. Azure IoT Edge device management automatically syncs the latest state of your devices after they’re reconnected to ensure seamless operability.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;IoT Edge security for your enterprise edge deployments&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Ensures that your devices have the right software and that only authorized edge devices can communicate with one another&#xA;Integrates with Azure Security Center to help provide end-to-end threat protection and security posture management&#xA;Supports any hardware security module to provide strong authenticated connections for confidential computing&#xA;Learn more about IoT Edge security&#xA;&#xA;IoT Edge pricing&#xA;&#xA;IoT Edge consists of the edge runtime, edge modules, and a cloud interface via Azure IoT Hub. The IoT Edge runtime is open source and free.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/DeveloperTools/AzureIotEdge.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
