<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDatabaseForPostgreSQL"
    id="e8946cb3-6902-4869-a2e9-c7c5f4245db1"
    documentation="Azure Database for PostgreSQL&#xA;Fully managed, intelligent, and scalable PostgreSQL&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/postgresql/&#xA;&#xA;Build massively scalable PostgreSQL applications&#xA;Focus on application innovation, not database management, with fully managed and intelligent Azure Database for PostgreSQL. Scale your workload quickly with ease and confidence.&#xA;&#xA;Azure Database for PostgreSQL Hyperscale is now Azure Arc-enabled. You can run this service on premises on infrastructure of your choice with cloud benefits like automation, hyperscale, unified management, and a cloud billing model with reserved capacity pricing now available.&#xA;&#xA;Integration with valuable Postgres features including JSONB, geospatial support, rich indexing, and dozens of extensions&#xA;&#xA;High-performance horizontal scaling on Postgres using Hyperscale (Citus)&#xA;&#xA;Intelligent performance recommendations generated from a custom analysis of your database&#xA;&#xA;Fully managed Postgres with Azure IP Advantage and Azure Advanced Threat Protection&#xA;&#xA;Innovate with open-source tools and extensions&#xA;Build or migrate your workloads with confidence using our fully managed service on community PostgreSQL. Use your favorite extensions, such as PLV8, PostGIS, and TimescaleDB, and popular frameworks and languages like Ruby on Rails, Python with Django, Java with Spring Boot, and Node.js. And use Microsoft open-source resources, including Citus Community on GitHub and the PostgreSQL extension (preview) for Azure Data Studio.&#xA;&#xA;Hyperscale your PostgreSQL database&#xA;Scale with ease to hundreds of nodes, with no application rewrites. Save time by running transactions and analytics in one database and avoid the costs of manual sharding. Stay up to date with the latest PostgreSQL innovations thanks to the Hyperscale (Citus) extension.&#xA;&#xA;Maximize database performance with ease&#xA;Do more with your application using customized performance recommendations. Use the query performance insight feature to monitor and detect disruptive events that can hamper performance.&#xA;&#xA;Protect your IP on a fully managed Azure service&#xA;Let Azure manage the time- and cost-intensive tasks associated with database maintenance, hosting, and high availability. Provision in minutes and independently scale compute or storage in seconds. Count on enterprise-grade security and compliance, and protect your innovation in the cloud with best-in-industry indemnification coverage via Azure IP Advantage.&#xA;&#xA;Advanced data security and compliance&#xA;&#xA;Discover, track, and remediate potential threats as they occur with advanced threat protection.&#xA;Control data isolation by configuring a virtual network.&#xA;Data is automatically encrypted at rest and in motion.&#xA;Azure Database for PostgreSQL is compliant with HIPAA, PCI DSS, FedRAMP, ISO, and more.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Databases/AzureDatabaseForPostgreSQL.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
