<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="RemoteRendering"
    id="ba99d1b0-fd56-4030-8daa-131856ae7411"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/remote-rendering/&#xA;Remote Rendering PREVIEW&#xA;Consume Services privately on Azure Platform&#xA;&#xA;Build interactive experiences with the highest quality 3D content&#xA;Azure Remote Rendering brings your highest quality 3D content and interactive experiences to mixed reality devices, such as HoloLens 2. This service uses the computing power of Azure to render even the most complex models in the cloud and streams them in real time to your devices, so users can interact and collaborate with 3D content in amazing detail.&#xA;Experience your 3D content in full detail&#xA;View and interact with your 3D models without decimation&#xA;Transcend the physical limits of your device&#xA;Render hundreds of millions of polygons and stream to mixed reality devices with low latency&#xA;Easily integrate into your application&#xA;A powerful SDK makes it easy to include remotely rendered content&#xA;&#xA;When every detail matters&#xA;&#xA;In scenarios where every detail matters—industrial plant management, design review for assets (such as truck engines), pre-operative surgery planning, and more—3D visualization brings that detail to life. It’s what helps designers, engineers, doctors, and students better understand complex information and make the right call.&#xA;&#xA;Experience 3D without compromise&#xA;&#xA;Bring incredibly detailed 3D models to the devices you use to work and collaborate without compromising quality. Oftentimes, you need to decimate and simplify high-quality 3D models to run on target hardware such as mobile devices and mixed reality headsets—resulting in loss of important detail needed in key business and design decisions. Azure Remote Rendering lets you view your models in original full detail without simplification or decimation.&#xA;&#xA;Easily integrate into your applications&#xA;&#xA;Easily extend your mixed reality apps with high-quality, remotely rendered 3D content using a powerful SDK.&#xA;"/>
