<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureBlockchainToken"
    id="fc23bea9-fdbb-4d19-a950-b4d19bf2810b"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/blockchain-tokens/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Blockchain Tokens PREVIEW&#xA;Easily define, create, and manage ledger-based tokens&#xA;&#xA;Build and define ledger-based tokens easily&#xA;Azure Blockchain Tokens Preview makes deploying and managing standard tokens easier than ever. It’s built on the standards developed by the Token Taxonomy Initiative, an open consortium of blockchain industry leaders. Confidently use tokens across blockchain networks in Azure, choosing from a growing set of initiative-compliant templates developed by Microsoft and partners.&#xA;Easily define and create Token Taxonomy Framework compliant tokens that represent digital or physical assets.&#xA;Manage enterprise-ready tokens with built-in security across ledgers, and use composable templates for common scenarios.&#xA;Incorporate business defined tokens into existing applications through a set of open SDKs.&#xA;Build tokens based on open community standards developed by blockchain experts.&#xA;&#xA;Play VideoPlay&#x9;&#xA;Current Time 0:00&#xA;Loaded: 0%Progress: 0%Seekbar Handle&#xA;/&#xA;Duration Time 0:25&#xA;Mute&#xA;Fullscreen&#xA;Accelerate your blockchain development&#xA;&#xA;Easily define, create, and manage compliant tokens. Transfer, transact, burn, or mint tokens more securely across counterparties, regardless of ledger choice. Benefit from composable templates for common scenarios developed by Microsoft and partners. Azure Key Vault and Azure Active Directory are integrated to help secure transactions.&#xA;&#xA;Explore the documentation&#xA;&#xA;Tap into an open and extensible framework&#xA;&#xA;Easily integrate Azure Blockchain Tokens into existing applications with an open API-driven interaction model. Simplify the building of your applications by abstracting your business logic from blockchain token infrastructure. Compliance with the Token Taxonomy Initiative ensures interoperability across Ethereum networks, with additional networks coming soon.&#xA;&#xA;Read the white paper&#xA;&#xA;Build on a standards-based foundation&#xA;&#xA;Azure Blockchain Tokens is based on the standards developed by the Token Taxonomy Initiative. These industry leaders are developing definitions and scope for a common standard for tokens with interchangeable, currency-like properties or unique assets.&#xA;&#xA;Contact the Token Taxonomy Initiative&#xA;Trusted by companies of all sizes&#xA;CEEK VR&#xA;&quot;CEEK Virtual Reality was looking for a trusted partner to help us with content viewership verification on the blockchain, and Azure Blockchain Tokens was perfect because it helped to drastically reduce our time to market and offered a trusted partner for providing proof on the blockchain.&quot;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Blockchain/png-initial-coin-offering-blockchain-token-transactions-per-second-scalability-summary-icon-blue-angle-text-trademark-clipart.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
