<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDataExplorer"
    id="d60b2b59-07be-4b33-b85c-1ada4fc23ea9"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/data-explorer/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Data Explorer&#xA;Fast and highly scalable data analytics service&#xA;&#xA;Overview&#xA;&#xA;Azure Data Explorer is a fast, fully managed data analytics service for real-time analysis on large volumes of data streaming from applications, websites, IoT devices, and more. Ask questions and iteratively explore data on the fly to improve products, enhance customer experiences, monitor devices, and boost operations. Quickly identify patterns, anomalies, and trends in your data. Explore new questions and get answers in minutes. Run as many queries as you need, thanks to the optimized cost structure.&#xA;An overview of Azure Data Explorer (ADX)&#xA;02-07-201919 min, 47 sec&#xA;Designed for data exploration&#xA;&#xA;Discover hidden insights from streaming data. The intuitive query language makes it easy to find answers quickly in rapidly changing data.&#xA;Fully managed for efficiency&#xA;&#xA;Explore new possibilities with your data cost effectively. Focus on insights, not infrastructure, with the easy-to-use, fully managed data analytics service.&#xA;Optimized for streaming data&#xA;&#xA;Respond quickly to fast-flowing and rapidly changing data. Azure Data Explorer simplifies analytics from all forms of streaming data.&#xA;Service capabilities&#xA;Low-latency ingestion&#xA;Elastically scale to terabytes of data in minutes. This data management service offers fast, low-latency ingestion with linear scaling that supports up to 200 MB of data per second per node. Azure Data Explorer supports a growing number of ingestion methods of data from devices, applications, servers, and services for your specific use cases.&#xA;Fast read-only query with high concurrency&#xA;Get results from 1 billion records in less than a second without modifying the data or metadata. Continue refining your queries until you’ve completed your analysis. Query large amounts of structured, semi-structured (JSON-like nested types), and unstructured (free-text) data. Search for specific text terms, locate events, and perform calculations on structured data. The intuitive query language uses Microsoft IntelliSense options and color coding to help you quickly spot patterns, trends, and anomalies. Simplify data exploration with fast text indexing, column store, and time-series operations all in one service.&#xA;Time-series analysis&#xA;Create and analyze thousands of time series in seconds with near-real-time monitoring solutions and workflows. Azure Data Explorer includes native support for creation, manipulation, and analysis of multiple time series.&#xA;Fully managed data service&#xA;Focus on the data instead of the infrastructure. This powerful, fully managed data analytics service automatically scales to meet your demands. Control costs by paying only for what you need, with no upfront costs or termination fees. Take advantage of the global availability for massive scalability.&#xA;Cost-effective queries and storage&#xA;Ask unlimited questions without skyrocketing costs; you pay by the hour, not by the query. You also control your storage costs. Get the best of a persistent database to automatically add data to the table, but with the flexibility to choose a retention policy based on how long you want to store the data. For persistent storage at commodity pricing, write data to Azure Blob Storage for future use.&#xA;Custom solutions with built-in analytics&#xA;Using our platform as a service (PaaS), build your own solution with interactive analytics built in. Azure Data Explorer is the data service for Azure Monitor, Azure Time Series Insights, and Windows Defender Advanced Threat Protection. It supports REST API, MS-TDS, and Azure Resource Manager service endpoints and several client libraries.&#xA;Use cases&#xA;IoT applications&#xA;IoT devices generate billions of sensor readings. Normalizing and aggregating data typically requires multiple technologies, which slows analysis, complicates maintenance, and leads to reliability issues. Azure Data Explorer facilitates remote monitoring of manufacturing equipment, vehicles, and systems that continuously cycle through operations. Derive insights from large volumes of telemetry to ensure high performance and optimize machine quality. Use the data for notifications and to feed analysis tools to diagnose and treat problems.&#xA;Big data logging platform&#xA;Publishers, ad networks, gaming sites, and other web-based businesses rely on large volumes of log data to spot trends, patterns, or anomalies in near-real time. With data exploration, discover insights that help you gain new customers, increase user engagement, and monetize traffic. Use this instant analysis of billions of lines of log data to generate personalized recommendations to visitors, predict which results and content suggestions they’re most likely to click on, and learn which content will lead to new subscriptions and purchases.&#xA;SaaS applications&#xA;Organizations are rapidly adopting software as a service (SaaS) applications for business transformation. Embed Azure Data Explorer in SaaS applications to ingest and analyze petabytes of data in real time. Developers are using this data to monitor service and improve application performance, while business users are discovering user trends, creating personalized experiences, and developing new revenue streams.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Analytics/AzureDataExplorer.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
