<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureSentinel"
    id="f87d75cf-78fe-4a1a-accd-a89b6268f10e"
    documentation="Azure Sentinel&#xA;Standing watch, by your side. Intelligent security analytics for your entire enterprise.&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/azure-sentinel/&#xA;&#xA;Build next-generation security operations with cloud and AI: See and stop threats before they cause harm, with SIEM reinvented for a modern world. Azure Sentinel is your birds-eye view across the enterprise. Put the cloud and large-scale intelligence from decades of Microsoft security experience to work. Make your threat detection and response smarter and faster with artificial intelligence (AI). Eliminate security infrastructure setup and maintenance, and elastically scale to meet your security needs—while reducing IT costs.&#xA;&#xA;Collect data at cloud scale—across all users, devices, applications, and infrastructure, both on-premises and in multiple clouds&#xA;&#xA;Detect previously uncovered threats and minimize false positives using analytics and unparalleled threat intelligence from Microsoft&#xA;&#xA;Investigate threats with AI and hunt suspicious activities at scale, tapping into decades of cybersecurity work at Microsoft&#xA;&#xA;Respond to incidents rapidly with built-in orchestration and automation of common tasks&#xA;&#xA;Limitless cloud speed and scale&#xA;Invest in security, not infrastructure setup and maintenance with the first cloud-native SIEM from a major cloud provider. Never again let a storage limit or a query limit prevent you from protecting your enterprise. Start using Azure Sentinel immediately, automatically scale to meet your organizational needs, and only pay for the resources you need.&#xA;&#xA;AI on your side&#xA;Focus on finding real threats quickly. Reduce noise from legitimate events with built-in machine learning and knowledge based on analyzing trillions of signals daily. Accelerate proactive threat hunting with pre-built queries based on years of security experience. View a prioritized list of alerts, get correlated analysis of thousands of security events within seconds, and visualize the entire scope of every attack. Simplify security operations and speed up threat response with integrated automation and orchestration of common tasks and workflows.&#xA;&#xA;Free Office 365 data import&#xA;Connect with data from your Microsoft products in just a few clicks, import Office 365 data for free, and analyze and draw correlations to deepen your intelligence.&#xA;&#xA;A match for all your tools&#xA;Connect to and collect data from all your sources including users, applications, servers, and devices running on-premises or in any cloud. Integrate with existing tools, whether business applications, other security products, or homegrown tools, and use your own machine-learning models. Optimize for your needs by bringing your own insights, tailored detections, machine learning models, and threat intelligence.&#xA;&#xA;A cost-effective, cloud-native SIEM with predictable billing and flexible commitments&#xA;Reduce infrastructure costs by automatically scaling resources and only paying for what you use. Save up to 60 percent as compared to pay-as-you-go pricing, through capacity reservation tiers. Receive predictable monthly bills and the flexibility to change your capacity tier commitment every 31 days. Pay nothing extra when you ingest data from Office 365 audit logs, Azure activity logs, and alerts from Microsoft threat protection solutions.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Security/AzureSentinel.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
