<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureHDInsight"
    id="6c902ac8-1ce0-4c4a-8d64-6aa1f044fca7"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/hdinsight/&#xA;HDInsight&#xA;Easy, cost-effective, enterprise-grade service  for open source analytics&#xA;&#xA;What are the benefits of HDInsight?&#xA;Easily run popular open source frameworks—including Apache Hadoop, Spark, and Kafka—using Azure HDInsight, a cost-effective, enterprise-grade service for open source analytics. Effortlessly process massive amounts of data and get all the benefits of the broad open source ecosystem with the global scale of Azure.&#xA;Quickly spin up big data clusters on demand, scale them up or down based on your usage needs, and pay only for what you use.&#xA;Use HDInsight tools to easily get started in your favorite development environment.&#xA;Meet industry and government compliance standards and protect your enterprise data assets using an Azure Virtual Network, encryption, and integration with Azure Active Directory.&#xA;HDInsight integrates seamlessly with other Azure services, including Data Factory and Data Lake Storage, for building comprehensive analytics pipelines.&#xA;Why HDInsight?&#xA;&#xA;Easy&#xA;Quickly spin up open source projects and clusters, with no hardware to install or infrastructure to manage.&#xA;&#xA;Cost-effective&#xA;Reduce costs by creating big data clusters on demand, easily scaling them up or down, and paying only for what you use.&#xA;&#xA;Enterprise-grade&#xA;Get enterprise-grade security and industry-leading compliance, with more than 30 certifications.&#xA;&#xA;Open&#xA;Create optimized components for Hadoop, Spark, and more. Keep up to date with the latest versions.&#xA;What comes with HDInsight?&#xA; Apache Hadoop&#xA;Apache Hadoop&#xA; Apache Spark&#xA;Apache Spark&#xA; Apache Kafka&#xA;Apache Kafka&#xA; Apache HBase&#xA;Apache HBase&#xA; Apache Hive LLAP&#xA;Apache Hive LLAP&#xA; Apache Storm&#xA;Apache Storm&#xA; Machine Learning&#xA;Machine Learning&#xA; &#xA;Open source ecosystem&#xA;HDInsight supports the latest open source projects from the Apache Hadoop and Spark ecosystems. Stay up to date with the newest releases of open source frameworks, including Kafka, HBase, and Hive LLAP.&#xA;&#xA;Security and compliance&#xA;Get enterprise-grade data protection with monitoring, virtual networks, encryption, Active Directory authentication, authorization, and role-based access control. HDInsight has more than 30 industry certifications, including ISO, SOC, HIPAA, and PCI, to meet compliance standards.&#xA;&#xA;Native integration with Azure services&#xA;Seamlessly integrate with a wide variety of Azure data stores and services, including Synapse Analytics, Azure Cosmos DB, Data Lake Storage, Blob Storage, Event Hubs, and Data Factory.&#xA;&#xA;Simplified monitoring&#xA;HDInsight integrates with Azure Log Analytics to provide a single interface where you can monitor all your clusters.&#xA;&#xA;Broad application support&#xA;HDInsight supports a broad range of applications from the big data ecosystem, which you can install with a single click. Pick from more than 30 popular Hadoop and Spark applications for a variety of scenarios.&#xA;&#xA;Multiple languages and tools&#xA;Use your preferred productivity tools, including Visual Studio, Eclipse, IntelliJ, Jupyter, and Zeppelin. Write code in familiar languages such as Scala, Python, R, JavaScript, and .NET.&#xA;Azure HDInsight Ecosystem&#xA;Tools&#xA;Apache Zeppelin&#xA;VS Code&#xA;IntelliJ&#xA;JDBC&#xA;Learn about Azure HDInsight tools&#xA;Data access&#xA;Batch&#xA;MapReduce&#xA;Apache Pig&#xA;Apache Spark&#xA;Apache Hive&#xA;SQL&#xA;Apache Hive LLAP&#xA;Apache Spark SQL&#xA;Apache Phoenix&#xA;NoSQL&#xA;Apache HBase&#xA;Stream&#xA;Apache Kafka&#xA;Apache Storm&#xA;Apache Spark&#xA;Machine Learning&#xA;MLib&#xA;Others&#xA;ISV apps&#xA;Azure Data Lake Storage&#xA;Security&#xA;Apache Ranger&#xA;Azure Active Directory&#xA;Virtual Network&#xA;Learn about Azure HDInsight security&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Analytics/AzureHDInsight.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
