<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureBastion"
    id="b8d5d907-9577-4e73-acf6-082691b6322e"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/azure-bastion/&#xA;Azure Bastion&#xA;Private and fully managed RDP and SSH access to your virtual machines&#xA;Managed RDP/SSH to VMs over SSL using private IP on the VM&#xA;Azure Bastion is a fully managed PaaS service that provides secure and seamless RDP and SSH access to your virtual machines directly through the Azure Portal. Azure Bastion is provisioned directly in your Virtual Network (VNet) and supports all VMs in your Virtual Network (VNet) using SSL without any exposure through public IP addresses.&#xA;&#xA;Connect your RDP and SSH sessions directly in the Azure Portal using a single click experience&#xA;&#xA;Log into your Azure virtual machines and avoid public Internet exposure using SSH and RDP with private IP addresses only&#xA;&#xA;Integrate and traverse existing firewalls and security perimeter using a modern HTML5 based web client and standard SSL ports&#xA;&#xA;Use your SSH keys for authentication when logging into your Azure virtual machines&#xA;&#xA;Limit public exposure of virtual machine IPs&#xA;&#xA;Access all virtual machines within a virtual network through a single hardened access point. Exposing the bastion host as primary exposed public access helps lockdown of public Internet exposure and limit threats such as port scanning and other types of malware targeting your VMs.&#xA;How to use Azure Bastion to connect securely to your Azure VMs&#xA;10-18-201909 min, 39 sec&#xA;Using Azure Bastion to connect securely to your Azure VMs&#xA;&#xA;Using a bastion host can help limit threats such as port scanning and other types of malware targeting your VMs. In this video, see how Azure Bastion gives you secure and seamless RDP and SSH access to your virtual machines. Now you can securely access your VMs over SSL from the Azure portal and without exposing public IP addresses.&#xA;&#xA;Play VideoPlay&#x9;&#xA;Current Time 0:00&#xA;Loaded: 0%Progress: 0%Seekbar Handle&#xA;/&#xA;Duration Time 1:03&#xA;Mute&#xA;Fullscreen&#xA;Fully managed bastion service&#xA;&#xA;Take advantage of a fully managed, autoscaling and hardened PaaS service, to provide you secure RDP and SSH connectivity. Seamless integration and easy one-time setup of Network Security Groups (ACLs) across your subnets, prevent subsequent and continuous management. Azure Bastion provides an integrated platform alternative to manually deploying and managing jump servers to shield your virtual machines. You can deploy Azure Bastion in just a few minutes and start using it instantly.&#xA;&#xA;RDP and SSH to Azure Virtual Machines over SSL&#xA;&#xA;With Azure Bastion, you can connect to your virtual machines in your virtual network over SSL, port 443, directly in Azure Portal. This enables clientless RDP/SSH connectivity so that you can connect from anywhere – any device and any platform, and without any additional agent running inside your virtual machines.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Networking/AzureBastion.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
