<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDataLakeAnalytics"
    id="cd6d412a-3c05-4f79-8d40-aad9710fe925"
    documentation="Data Lake Analytics&#xA;An on-demand analytics job service to power intelligent action&#xA;&#xA;Azure Data Lake Analytics is an on-demand analytics job service that simplifies big data&#xA;Easily develop and run massively parallel data transformation and processing programs in U-SQL, R, Python, and .NET over petabytes of data. With no infrastructure to manage, you can process data on demand, scale instantly, and only pay per job.&#xA;Start in seconds, scale instantly, pay per job&#xA;Process big data jobs in seconds with Azure Data Lake Analytics. There is no infrastructure to worry about because there are no servers, virtual machines, or clusters to wait for, manage, or tune. Instantly scale the processing power, measured in Azure Data Lake Analytics Units (AU), from one to thousands for each job. You only pay for the processing that you use per job.&#xA;Develop massively parallel programs with simplicity&#xA;U-SQL is a simple, expressive, and extensible language that allows you to write code once and have it automatically parallelized for the scale you need. Process petabytes of data for diverse workload categories such as querying, ETL, analytics, machine learning, machine translation, image processing, and sentiment analysis by leveraging existing libraries written in .NET languages, R, or Python. Watch the U-SQL query execution for Azure Data Lake video to see how we detect the type of objects in one million images using a U-SQL built-in cognitive library.&#xA;Debug and optimize your big data programs with ease&#xA;Debug failures in cloud distributed programs as easily as debugging a program in your personal environment. Our execution environment actively analyzes your programs as they run and gives you recommendations to improve performance and reduce cost. For example, if you request 1000 AUs for your program and only 50 AUs are needed, the system recommends that you only use 50 AUs—reducing the cost by 95%.&#xA;Virtualize your analytics&#xA;Act on all of your data with optimized data virtualization of your relational sources such as Azure SQL Database and Azure Synapse Analytics. Your queries are automatically optimized by moving processing close to the source data without data movement, which maximizes performance and minimizes latency.&#xA;Enterprise-grade security, auditing, and support&#xA;Extend your on-premises security and governance controls to the cloud, and meet your security and regulatory compliance needs. Single sign-on (SSO), multi-factor authentication, and seamless management of millions of identities are built-in through Azure Active Directory. Role-based access control and the ability to audit all processing and management operations are on by default. We guarantee a 99.9% enterprise-grade SLA and 24/7 support for your big data solution.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Analytics/AzureDataLakeAnalytics.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
