<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDatabaseForMariaDB"
    id="c0cdbe16-1991-42f5-b7fd-357a1397142c"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/mariadb/&#xA;Azure Database for MariaDB&#xA;Enterprise-ready, fully managed community MariaDB&#xA;Easily deploy applications to the cloud using your choice of languages and frameworks.&#xA;Achieve business continuity and dynamically respond to changes in customer demand with built-in high availability and elastic scaling.&#xA;Get unparalleled security and compliance, including Azure IP Advantage, and industry-leading reach through a global network of Microsoft datacenters.&#xA;Flexible pricing: Choose the right resources for your workloads, with no hidden costs.&#xA;&#xA;Community MariaDB that’s fully managed&#xA;&#xA;Combine MariaDB Community edition with the benefits of a fully managed service provider to free developers from complex infrastructure and database management so they can focus on building exceptional apps.&#xA;&#xA;Languages and frameworks of your choice&#xA;&#xA;Azure Database for MariaDB works with popular open-source frameworks and languages, and features tight integration with Azure Web Apps. Use it with popular content management apps, such as WordPress and Drupal, for a fully integrated experience that supports your specific application development needs.&#xA;&#xA;Built-in high availability&#xA;&#xA;Trust Azure to keep enterprise apps up and running. Built to deliver high availability with a service-level agreement (SLA) of 99.99 percent, Azure Database for MariaDB requires no extra configuration, replication, or cost to ensure that your apps run when you need them to.&#xA;&#xA;Scale within seconds&#xA;&#xA;Provision in minutes, and flexibly scale your compute or storage independently, within seconds.&#xA;&#xA;Simple and flexible pricing&#xA;&#xA;Azure Database for MariaDB provides the database management capabilities you need—like automatic patching, automatic backups, and built-in monitoring and security—at no extra cost.&#xA;&#xA;Unmatched security and reach&#xA;&#xA;Run your apps on world-class infrastructure and the world's most trusted cloud. As a fully integrated service, Azure Database for MariaDB plugs you into the Microsoft global network of datacenters with unparalleled security and around-the-clock monitoring.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Databases/AzureDatabaseForMariaDB.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
