<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureContentProtection"
    id="364a7f0c-634f-486c-ab45-6ab49af049f5"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/media-services/content-protection/&#xA;&#xA;Content Protection&#xA;Deliver highly-secure content using multi-DRM (PlayReady, Widevine, FairPlay Streaming) or AES clear key encryption&#xA;&#xA;Secure content from cloud upload to playback&#xA;Use AES clear key and multi-DRM (PlayReady, Widevine, and FairPlay Streaming)&#xA;Simplify key management and allow dynamic encryption on the fly&#xA;Integrate with Active Directory or your own authentication system&#xA;Configure protection rules with simple APIs or web portal&#xA;Deliver highly-secure playback with native HTML5 or client SDKs for all device&#xA;Quickly configure key/license delivery&#xA;Setting up and configuring a DRM license server in your system can be complicated. Azure Content Protection lets you set up major DRM license delivery (Microsoft PlayReady, Widevine, and FairPlay Streaming) in minutes. You define what type of licenses you want and we handle the infrastructure, security, and scalability.&#xA;Encrypt media content on the fly&#xA;Azure Media Services gives you on-the-fly encryption for video on demand (VOD) and live streams. It’s also more cost-effective than traditional static encryption and packaging, because Media Services stores only one copy of standard multiple-bitrate MP4s and employs dynamic encryption. If your content key is ever compromised, simply call our APIs to change the key instead of re-encrypting your entire library.&#xA;Supports leading industry standards&#xA;Most modern browsers support the Encrypted Media Extensions (EME) standard for playing back encrypted content in HTML5. Media Services enables Common Encryption (CENC) on MPEG-DASH streams with PlayReady and Widevine DRM technologies, which is supported on various players, including Azure Media Player. Media Services also enables you to protect your content with FairPlay Streaming DRM for Apple TV streaming.&#xA;Works seamlessly with Azure Active Directory&#xA;Content Protection gives you token-based authorization for all types of key/licenses delivery. You can use JSON Web Token (JWT) or Simple Web Token (SWT) to add or validate claims for your customers. Also, for Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) customers, we've released sample code with detailed instructions to guide you through using Azure AD to authorize your content.&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Media/AzureContentProtection.jpg"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
