<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureActiveDirectoryDomainServices"
    id="82963ccc-6a35-4425-805b-a9bcc1e491cd"
    documentation="Your domain controller as a service&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/active-directory-ds/&#xA;Lift-and-shift apps to Azure more easily than ever&#xA;Get started in minutes, pay as you go&#xA;Use LDAP, Azure Active Directory domain join, NTLM, and Kerberos authentication&#xA;Develop and test with no identity worries&#xA;Rely on a managed, highly-available service&#xA;Manage Azure virtual machines effectively using Group Policy&#xA;&#xA;Use managed domain services on Azure&#xA;Use Azure Active Directory Domain Services to join Azure virtual machines to a domain, without having to deploy domain controllers. Sign in to the virtual machines using their corporate Azure Active Directory credentials and seamlessly access resources. Use Group Policy to more securely administer domain-joined virtual machines—a familiar way to apply and enforce security baselines on all of your Azure virtual machines.&#xA;&#xA;Migrate on-premises apps to Azure with no identity worries&#xA;Take advantage of Azure Active Directory Domain Services features like domain join, LDAP, NT LAN Manager (NTLM), and Kerberos authentication, which are widely used in enterprises. Migrate legacy directory-aware applications running on-premises to Azure, without having to worry about identity requirements. On Linux and Windows Server virtual machines on Azure, easily deploy line-of-business applications. You don’t have to deploy domain controllers as Azure virtual machines or use a VPN connection back to your identity infrastructure.&#xA;&#xA;Deploy in minutes with enterprise-grade performance&#xA;Use the Azure portal to quickly enable Azure Active Directory Domain Services for your Azure AD tenant. Select your performance level and take advantage of enterprise-grade features such as resource forests and daily back ups.&#xA;&#xA;Get enterprise scale and SLA&#xA;Azure Active Directory Domain Services gives you enterprise-grade scale and reliability. It’s a highly-available service hosted in globally-distributed datacenters.&#xA;&#xA;Handle traditional directory-aware apps along with SaaS apps&#xA;Azure Active Directory, the identity and access management cloud solution for your employees, partners, and consumers, supports your traditional directory-aware apps alongside your modern cloud apps.&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Identity/AzureActiveDirectoryDomainServices.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
