<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="VisualStudioCode"
    id="fcea6289-2c58-46e9-9771-0ecd46bc6f86"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/products/visual-studio-code/&#xA; powerful, lightweight free code editor with integrated tools to easily deploy your code to Azure&#xA;Download now &#xA;Try Azure for free&#xA;One editor, from code to cloud&#xA;Spend more time coding and less time switching between tools. Use features and extensions that integrate with Azure and GitHub to develop, debug, and deploy all from one place.&#xA;&#xA;Provides local emulators and extensions to build, run, and debug cloud apps directly from the editor&#xA;Imports and manages data for local or remote databases, with support for Azure Cosmos DB, MongoDB, and more&#xA;Has guided workflows for Azure Pipelines to create and configure continuous integration&#xA;Supports nearly every language and app type, including static web apps, serverless Azure Functions, and Kubernetes clusters&#xA;Develop cloud apps locally before you deploy Pause gif Playing gif&#xA;Develop cloud apps locally before you deploy&#xA;&#xA;Create, run, and debug your cloud projects locally so you can prototype quickly. Optimize costs by testing whether new features run efficiently in the cloud before deploying. Azure extensions include emulators for Azure Storage, Azure Cosmos DB, and Azure Functions.&#xA;Set up automated deployments to the cloud Pause gif Playing gif&#xA;Set up automated deployments to the cloud&#xA;&#xA;Use the Deploy to Azure extension to set up continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) from your apps to the cloud using GitHub Actions or Azure Pipelines. Easily create a CI/CD pipeline targeting Azure App Service, Azure Functions, or Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) using the extension’s built-in automated workflows.&#xA;&#xA;Read tutorial&#xA;Add and manage data Pause gif Playing gif&#xA;Add and manage data&#xA;&#xA;Easily manage your app’s data using the built-in MongoDB and IntelliSense support. Connect to your local or remote MongoDB servers and manage databases, collections, and documents, or host them in the cloud with the Azure Cosmos DB free tier.&#xA;&#xA;Read the documentation&#xA;Collaborate with ease Pause gif Playing gif&#xA;Collaborate with ease&#xA;&#xA;You don’t need to change how you work with others, whether they’re teammates in the same room or community developers around the world. Bring pull requests into the editor, where you have full editing and debugging support with the GitHub Pull Requests extension. Or collaborate on editing, debugging, and app sharing in real time for pair programming or code reviews with the Live Share Extension Pack.&#xA;Containers&#xA;Build, manage, and deploy containerized applications using the Docker extension. Generate docker files from your existing repository and manage your containers, images, and registries from inside Visual Studio Code.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Kubernetes&#xA;Enjoy a fully integrated Kubernetes experience with the Kubernetes extension. Deploy containerized applications to local or cloud-hosted Kubernetes clusters and debug your live applications in Visual Studio Code.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Front-end web development&#xA;Extend JavaScript debugging to front-end development using the Debugger for Microsoft Edge extension. Set breakpoints and step through front-end JavaScript code to resolve issues quickly. Debug front-end and back-end code simultaneously with the multitarget debugging ">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/DeveloperTools/VisualStudioCode.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
