<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureNetAppFiles"
    id="e30fbc8d-b49d-4e8a-8bd5-502e94b80522"
    documentation="Azure NetApp Files&#xA;Enterprise file storage, powered by NetApp&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/netapp/&#xA;Run your most demanding Linux and Windows file workloads in Azure&#xA;Running performance-intensive and latency-sensitive file workloads in the cloud can be hard. Azure NetApp Files makes it easy for enterprise line-of-business (LOB) and storage professionals to migrate and run complex, file-based applications with no code change. Azure NetApp Files is widely used as the underlying shared file-storage service in various scenarios. These include migration (lift and shift) of POSIX-compliant Linux and Windows applications, SAP HANA, databases, high-performance compute (HPC) infrastructure and apps, and enterprise web applications.&#xA;&#xA;Support for multiple protocols enables lift and shift of both Linux and Windows apps to run seamlessly in Azure&#xA;&#xA;Multiple performance tiers allow for close alignment with workload performance requirements&#xA;&#xA;Deep integration with Azure enables a seamless and highly secure Azure experience, with no learning or management overhead&#xA;&#xA;Leading certifications, including SAP HANA, GDPR, and HIPPA, enable migration of the most demanding workloads to Azure&#xA;&#xA;Get extreme file performance&#xA;Migrate and run your most demanding Linux and Windows file workloads in Azure, powered by NetApp’s industry-leading technology.&#xA;&#xA;Get bare-metal performance, sub-millisecond latency, and integrated data management for your complex enterprise workloads, including SAP HANA, HPC, LOB applications, high-performance file shares, and virtual desktop infrastructure (VDI).&#xA;&#xA;Simplify storage management&#xA;Set up in minutes and manage seamlessly, as with any other Azure service, using the familiar Azure portal experience, CLI, PowerShell, or REST API. Support for multiple file-storage protocols in a single service, including NFSv3, NFSv4.1, and SMB3.1.x, enables a wide range of application lift-and-shift scenarios, with no need for code changes.&#xA;&#xA;Azure NetApp Files comes with three performance tiers: Standard, Premium, and Ultra. These can be provisioned with a simple click, allowing unmatched flexibility.&#xA;&#xA;Migrate with confidence&#xA;Gain peace of mind with the industry’s leading security and compliance portfolio. Critical capabilities in this area include FIPS-140-2-compliant data encryption at rest, role-based access control (RBAC), Active Directory authentication, and export policies for network-based access control lists (ACLs).&#xA;&#xA;Azure NetApp Files complies with leading industry certifications, like HIPPA and GDPR. With default 99.99-percent availability, this means you can migrate and run industry applications in Azure with confidence.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Storage/AzureNetAppFiles.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
