<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureLabServices"
    id="58580540-0564-404a-8719-b5b58b19f695"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/lab-services/&#xA;&#xA;Create a lab of preconfigured virtual machines&#xA;Easily set up and provide on-demand access to preconfigured virtual machines (VMs) to support your scenarios. Teach a class, train professionals, run a hackathon or a hands-on lab, and more. Simply define your needs and the service will roll the lab out to your audience. Users access all their lab VMs from a single place.&#xA;Immediate access to VMs for invited users, with no need to share your Azure subscription&#xA;Custom templates to quickly provision lab VMs and use repeatedly across labs&#xA;Scheduling feature to automatically shut down and start VMs and limit usage hours&#xA;Provisioning and scaling to hundreds of VMs with a single click—with the service managing all underlying infrastructure&#xA;&#xA;Simple user experience&#xA;&#xA;Invite users to access lab resources right away. When they sign in, they’ll see a full list of VMs they can access across multiple labs. With one click they can connect and start working—no Azure subscription needed.&#xA;&#xA;Cost optimization and tracking&#xA;&#xA;Manage your lab budget with usage control features. Schedule designated usage times or set up recurring auto-shutdowns and start times. Track individuals’ hourly usage or limit usage by setting up quotas.&#xA;&#xA;Automatic management and scaling&#xA;&#xA;As a managed service, Lab Services gives you automatic provisioning and management of your lab’s underlying infrastructure. Just prepare the right lab experience for your users and the service will handle the rest—rolling out and scaling your lab to hundreds of VMs with a single click.&#xA;When to use Azure Lab Services&#xA;Classes or professional training&#xA;Configure lab VMs with the right content and give each user a set number of hours to complete their homework or projects.&#xA;Hackathons and hands-on labs&#xA;Create interactive experiences at conferences and events. Scale up to hundreds of VMs to meet demand.&#xA;Customer trials and demos&#xA;Create invitation-only private labs for demoing your prerelease software.&#xA;Developer machines and test environments&#xA;Provision multi-resource environments that consist of platform as a service (PaaS) and VM resources in our closely related Azure DevTest Labs. Share preconfigured resources or enable users to create their ">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/DevOps/AzureLabServices.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
