<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDatabaseForMySQL"
    id="7a87af15-b7a6-451d-8551-8dfec0cda9df"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/mysql/&#xA;Azure Database for MySQL&#xA;Enterprise-ready, fully managed community MySQL&#xA;&#xA;Azure Database for MySQL provides fully managed, enterprise-ready community MySQL database as a service. The MySQL Community edition helps you easily lift and shift to the cloud, using languages and frameworks of your choice. On top of that, you get built-in high availability and dynamic scaling, helping you easily adjust to changes in customer demands. Additionally, you benefit from the unparalleled security and compliance, including Azure IP advantage, as well as Azure’s industry leading reach. All this with a flexible pricing model so you can choose resources for your workload with no hidden cost.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Community MySQL that’s fully managed&#xA;&#xA;Combine MySQL Community edition with the benefits of a fully managed service provider, and free developers from the complexity of infrastructure and database management so they can focus on building exceptional apps.&#xA;&#xA;Languages and frameworks of your choice&#xA;&#xA;Azure Database for MySQL enables popular open source frameworks and languages, and it features tight integration with Azure Web Apps. Popular content management apps, such as WordPress and Drupal, deliver a fully integrated experience supporting your application development needs.&#xA;&#xA;Scale in seconds with built-in high availability&#xA;&#xA;Provision in minutes, and flexibly scale compute or storage independently within seconds. Built to deliver high availability with an SLA of 99.99 percent, Azure Database for MySQL requires no extra configuration, replicatio¬n, or cost to ensure that your apps run when you need them to.&#xA;&#xA;Protect your database with built-in intelligence&#xA;&#xA;Azure Database for MySQL offers Advanced Threat Protection, which monitors your database around the clock and detects potential malicious activities, alerting you upon detection so you can intervene right away.&#xA;&#xA;Simple and flexible pricing&#xA;&#xA;Everything you need is included with simple, flexible pricing. Azure Database for MySQL provides capabilities you want—like automatic database patching, automatic backups, built-in monitoring, security, and more—at no extra cost.&#xA;&#xA;Unparalleled security and reach&#xA;&#xA;Run your apps on world-class infrastructure and the world's most trusted cloud. As a fully integrated service, Azure Database for MySQL plugs you into the Microsoft global network of datacenters, unparalleled security, and round-the-clock monitoring.&#xA;&#xA;Intelligent apps&#xA;Develop sophisticated, transformational apps using state-of-the-art machine-learning algorithms and integrated visualization tools to get actionable insights and analytics.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Retail and e-commerce&#xA;Build secure and scalable e-commerce solutions that meet the demands of both customers and businesses. Engage customers through customized products and offers, process transactions quickly and securely, and focus on fulfillment and customer service.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Scalable web and mobile applications&#xA;Rapidly build engaging and scalable cross-platform and native apps for iOS, Android, Windows, or Mac.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Digital marketing&#xA;Engage with customers around the world with rich, personalized digital marketing experiences. Quickly build and launch digital campaigns that automatically scale based on customer demand.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Finance management apps&#xA;Securely store critical data and provide high-value analytics and insights over aggregated data to users, using in-built security and performance.&#xA;&#xA;Gaming&#xA;Scale your databases elastically to accommodate unpredictable bursts of traffic and deliver low-latency multi-player experiences.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Databases/AzureDatabaseForMySQL.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
