<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureMediaServices"
    id="81743882-b18c-4cae-9cc7-a7424d3f1772"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/media-services/&#xA;Azure Media Services&#xA;Cloud-based media workflow platform to index, package, protect, and stream video at scale&#xA;&#xA;Manage, transform, and deliver media content with cloud-based workflows&#xA;Use high-definition video encoding and streaming services to reach your audiences on the devices they use. And enhance content discoverability and performance with AI. All while helping to protect your content with digital rights management (DRM).&#xA;Multi-channel pipeline that orchestrates video and audio analysis and incorporates cues into a single timeline.&#xA;Web interface for easy evaluation and integration, plus easy-to-use web widgets and REST APIs.&#xA;Intuitive customization and management features, letting you train and fine-tune selected models to improve indexing accuracy.&#xA;Compliance with regulations including HIPAA, ISO 27001-27018, FedRAMP, HITRUST, and PCI.&#xA;&#xA;Boost media discoverability and performance&#xA;&#xA;Increase the discoverability of your audio and video content by automatically extracting advanced metadata. Enhance your apps with new forms of detectable content like spoken words, written text, and faces, as well as speakers, celebrities, and emotions.&#xA;&#xA;Explore Video Indexer&#xA;&#xA;Support your modern content distribution&#xA;&#xA;Deliver a range of media source file and content streaming and protection formats to client technologies like HTTP Live Streaming (HLS), MPEG-DASH, and Smooth Streaming. Use Azure Media Player to deliver content—applying industry standards like HTML5, media source extensions, and encrypted media extensions and providing an enriched, adaptive cloud streaming experience.&#xA;&#xA;Azure Media Player&#xA;Encoding&#xA;Dynamic packaging&#xA;&#xA;Scale delivery according to your needs&#xA;&#xA;Live broadcast a town hall or company meeting, a webinar, or a large sporting event to any online audience. Azure Media Services handles audiences of all sizes while you control the properties of the outgoing video livestream, such as how much is recorded and whether or not viewers can start watching.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more&#xA;Help protect your content&#xA;Deliver content dynamically encrypted with Advanced Encryption Standard (AES-128) or your choice of popular DRM systems, including Microsoft PlayReady, Google Widevine, and Apple FairPlay. Azure Media Services also delivers AES keys and DRM licenses to authorized clients.&#xA;&#xA;Drive professional standards&#xA;Microsoft Azure is the first hyperscale cloud to be formally assessed by the Motion Picture Association of America, certified by the Content Delivery and Security Association, and audited by the Federation Against Copyright Theft.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Media/AzureMediaServices.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
