<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="WindowsVirtualDesktop"
    id="03c468c8-d00a-4a8c-9931-ac7e5fff3d9c"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/virtual-desktop/&#xA;Quickly deploy virtual desktops and apps to enable secure remote work&#xA;Deploy and scale virtualized Windows desktops and apps on Azure&#xA;Windows Virtual Desktop is a comprehensive desktop and app virtualization service running in the cloud. It’s the only virtual desktop infrastructure (VDI) that delivers simplified management, multi-session Windows 10, optimizations for Office 365 ProPlus, and support for Remote Desktop Services (RDS) environments. Deploy and scale your Windows desktops and apps on Azure in minutes, and get built-in security and compliance features.&#xA;&#xA;Deliver the only multi-session Windows 10 virtual desktop experience&#xA;Provide your users with the only multi-session Windows 10 desktop virtualized in the cloud that’s highly scalable, always up to date, and available on any device.&#xA;&#xA;Enable optimizations for Office 365 ProPlus&#xA;Deliver the best Office 365 ProPlus experience, with multi-session virtual desktop scenarios to provide the most productive virtualized experience for your users.&#xA;&#xA;Migrate Windows Server remote desktops and apps to Azure&#xA;Migrate your Remote Desktop Services (RDS) environment with simplified management and deployment experience on Azure.&#xA;&#xA;Deploy and scale in minutes&#xA;Quickly virtualize and deploy modern and legacy desktop apps to the cloud in minutes with unified management in the Azure portal.&#xA;&#xA;More secure, productive virtual desktop experience on Azure with Microsoft 365&#xA;&#xA;Deploy a complete, intelligent solution that enhances creativity and collaboration for everyone. Shift to Microsoft 365 and get Office 365, Windows 10, and Enterprise Mobility + Security.&#xA;&#xA;Flexible migration to the cloud for Remote Desktop Services&#xA;&#xA;Optimize your cloud experience while lowering costs for your Windows Server desktops and apps. Get all the tools and resources you need to migrate your apps, data, and infrastructure at your own pace, with confidence.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Supported transition to Windows 10&#xA;&#xA;Get free extended security updates for your Windows 7 virtual desktop on Azure with Windows Virtual Desktop. Also, check application compatibility with Microsoft FastTrack App Assure. The program provides no-cost app compatibility assistance when deploying Windows 10 and Windows 10 multi-session with Windows Virtual Desktop.&#xA;&#xA;Windows Virtual Desktop for dev/test environments&#xA;&#xA;Enable development and testing scenarios including virtual developer desktops and simplified load and scale testing virtual machine (VM) management Windows Virtual Desktop. Leverage the service to rapidly test .NET, UWP and other types of apps including end user acceptance testing for critical line of business (LOB) apps.&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/VirtualDesktop/AzureVirtualDesktop.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
