<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDatabaseMigrationService"
    id="4fef36ef-e0f0-4a24-a5d6-4736f8a93602"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/database-migration/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Database Migration Service&#xA;A simple tool to accelerate your data migration to Azure&#xA;&#xA;Ease your database migration to Azure&#xA;Azure Database Migration Service is a tool that helps you simplify, guide, and automate your database migration to Azure. Easily migrate your data, schema, and objects from multiple sources to the cloud at scale.&#xA;Starting database workload migrations? Go to Azure Migrate to discover and assess on-premises applications and data&#xA;Database-sensitive migration moves data, schema, and objects to Azure&#xA;Easy-to-understand process helps you get the job done right the first time&#xA;Supports Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, and Oracle migration to Azure from on-premises and other clouds&#xA;Highly resilient and self-healing migration service provides reliable outcomes with near-zero downtime&#xA;&#xA;Execute a complete migration with near-zero downtime&#xA;&#xA;Migrate your database and server objects—including user accounts, agent jobs, and SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS) packages—all at once with almost no downtime.&#xA;&#xA;Get step-by-step guidance&#xA;&#xA;Move widely used databases&#xA;&#xA;Migrate your data to Azure from the most common database management systems. Whether you’re moving from an on-premises database or another cloud, Database Migration Service supports key migration scenarios such as SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, and Oracle.&#xA;&#xA;Automate your database migrations&#xA;&#xA;Save time and effort by automating your move to Azure with PowerShell. Database Migration Service works with PowerShell commandlets to automatically migrate a list of databases.&#xA;&#xA;Play VideoPlay&#x9;&#xA;Current Time 0:00&#xA;Loaded: 0%Progress: 0%Seekbar Handle&#xA;/&#xA;Duration Time 27:49&#xA;Mute&#xA;Fullscreen&#xA;Simplify your migration with a two-step process&#xA;&#xA;Better prepare your database workloads to move to Azure using the suite of Azure migration tools. First, use Azure Migrate to discover your on-premises data estate, assess migration readiness, and choose the best destination for your databases. Then, use Database Migration Service to move your on-premises databases to Azure.&#xA;&#xA;Watch a demo of the end-to-end process&#xA;"/>
