<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureBoards"
    id="54f1d383-d6fe-4692-8cf1-358c26ff0f8f"
    documentation="Azure Boards&#xA;Track work with configurable Kanban boards, interactive backlogs, and powerful planning tools. Unparalleled traceability and reporting make Boards the perfect home for all your ideas—big and small.&#xA;&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/devops/boards/&#xA;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/devops/learn/compare/azure-boards-vs-jira&#xA;&#xA;Track work with Kanban boards, backlogs, team dashboards, and custom reporting&#xA;Combine drag-and-drop sprint planning and flexible work item tracking with comprehensive traceability to have the perfect home for all your ideas–big and small.&#xA;&#xA;Connected from idea to release&#xA;Track all your ideas at every development stage and keep your team aligned with all code changes linked directly to work items.&#xA;Scrum ready&#xA;Use built-in scrum boards and planning tools to help your teams run sprints, stand-ups, and planning meetings.&#xA;Built for insights&#xA;Gain new insights into the health and status of your project with powerful analytics tools and dashboard widgets.&#xA;&#xA;Already using GitHub? Try Azure Boards Integration.&#xA;Boost your team's productivity with Boards, Backlogs, and Sprints for even the most complex project. Simply connect your GitHub repo to Azure Boards and start linking commits and PRs to work items.&#xA;&#xA;Start planning your next sprint with Boards&#xA;Use proven productivity tools&#xA;Get your work done with simple and modern agile tools like Kanban boards, backlogs, dashboards, and scrum boards. Adapt the tools to fit your team’s needs and scale up easily.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Customize your dashboards&#xA;Build tailored views of the data you need, configure the layout that makes sense for your team, and easily monitor progress throughout the lifecycle of your project.&#xA;Choose your workflow&#xA;Start with a simple, out-of-the-box workflow. Use the powerful and flexible customization engine to create the workflow that fits your team’s needs.&#xA;&#xA;Use with your favorite tools&#xA;Azure Boards works with your favorite tools. Integrate with Microsoft Teams and Slack to enable efficient ChatOps.&#xA;Extensions Marketplace&#xA;Access 1,000+ extensions or create your own.&#xA;View all extensions&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/DevOps/AzureBoards.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
