<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureMonitor"
    id="e801256d-0a1d-4479-baeb-3ed8435a8725"
    documentation="Full observability into your applications, infrastructure, and network&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/monitor/&#xA;&#xA;Transform your business with modern monitoring&#xA;Collect, analyze, and act on telemetry data from your Azure and on-premises environments. Azure Monitor helps you maximize performance and availability of your applications and proactively identify problems in seconds.&#xA;&#xA;Unified: Store and analyze all your operational telemetry in a centralized, fully managed, scalable data store that’s optimized for performance and cost.&#xA;&#xA;Intelligent: Test your hypotheses and reveal hidden patterns using the advanced analytic engine, interactive query language, and built-in machine learning constructs.&#xA;&#xA;Open: Integrate with popular DevOps, issue management, IT service management, and security information and event management tools.&#xA;&#xA;Monitor your applications: Get everything you need to monitor the availability, performance, and usage of your web applications, whether they're hosted on Azure or on-premises. Azure Monitor supports popular languages and frameworks, such as .NET, Java, and Node.js, and integrates with DevOps processes and tools like Azure DevOps, Jira, and PagerDuty. Track live metrics streams, requests and response times, and events.&#xA;&#xA;Monitor your infrastructure: Analyze and optimize the performance of your infrastructure, including virtual machines (VMs), Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), Azure Storage, and databases. Monitor your Linux and Windows VMs and their health and dependencies—all on a single map.&#xA;&#xA;Monitor your network: Monitor and diagnose networking issues without logging into your virtual machines. Trigger a packet capture, diagnose routing issues, analyze network security group flow logs, and gain visibility and control over your Azure network.&#xA;&#xA;How Azure Monitor works: Azure Monitor collects monitoring telemetry from a variety of on-premises and Azure sources. Management tools, such as those in Azure Security Center and Azure Automation, also push log data to Azure Monitor. The service aggregates and stores this telemetry in a log data store that’s optimized for cost and performance. Analyze data, set up alerts, get end-to-end views of your applications, and use machine learning–driven insights to quickly identify and resolve problems.&#xA;&#xA;Gain insights from your data: Use the powerful analytics platform and extensive query language to analyze, interact with, and derive insights from huge volumes of operational data in seconds. Isolate anomalies and detect problems quickly using smart analytics and machine learning algorithms.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Management/AzureMonitor.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
