<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureBlockchainService"
    id="cc6e08dc-4318-455f-88cd-6bb216dc4c55"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/blockchain-service/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Blockchain Service&#xA;Build, govern, and expand consortium blockchain networks&#xA;&#xA;The foundation for blockchain apps in the cloud&#xA;Build, govern, and expand blockchain networks at scale. Azure Blockchain Service Preview simplifies the formation, management, and governance of consortium blockchain networks so you can focus on business logic and app development.&#xA;Deploy fully managed blockchain networks in a few simple clicks&#xA;Govern at scale with built-in governance and codeless consortia management&#xA;Build blockchain apps with confidence using the dev tools you love and the apps you rely on today&#xA;Capture, react to, and store ledger data off-chain using blockchain data manager for end-to-end solutions&#xA;&#xA;Simple blockchain network deployment and operations&#xA;&#xA;Create and configure consortium blockchain infrastructure quickly and offload network management while maintaining the ability to update over time.&#xA;&#xA;See how to build your blockchain network&#xA;&#xA;Play VideoPlay&#x9;&#xA;Current Time 0:00&#xA;Loaded: 0%Progress: 0%Seekbar Handle&#xA;/&#xA;Duration Time 0:20&#xA;Mute&#xA;Fullscreen&#xA;Built-in consortium management&#xA;&#xA;Get full node management and govern consortia at scale. Modular controls provide easy member onboarding, codeless permissioning, and simplified policy enforcement.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about network governance&#xA;&#xA;Easy blockchain data publishing&#xA;&#xA;Build end-to-end solutions using blockchain data manager. Get flexible, reliable, and scalable data streaming and application integration with a few clicks. Monitor your smart contracts, react to transactions and events, and stream on-chain data to off-chain data stores.&#xA;&#xA;Explore blockchain data manager&#xA;&#xA;Open and extensible design&#xA;&#xA;Build blockchain applications with confidence on an open, flexible platform that integrates with the dev tools, data sources, and applications you already use.&#xA;&#xA;Explore a solution architecture&#xA;Innovate with confidence&#xA;Microsoft invests over USD1 billion annually on cybersecurity research and development.&#xA;&#xA;We employ more than 3,500 security experts focused on securing data and privacy.&#xA;&#xA;Azure has more certifications than any other cloud provider. View the full list.&#xA; &#xA;ISO/IEC&#xA; &#xA;CSA/CCm&#xA; &#xA;ITAR&#xA; &#xA;CJIS&#xA; &#xA;HIPAA&#xA; &#xA;IRS 1075&#xA;Learn more about Azure security&#xA;&#xA;Azure Blockchain Service offers simple per-node pricing&#xA;&#xA;Customize your blockchain network infrastructure while keeping costs predictable.&#xA;&#xA;Azure Blockchain Service is now available in two tiers. Basic provides a cost-optimized environment for developing and testing your blockchain apps. Standard can be used to run production blockchain networks with built-in high availability.&#xA;&#xA;See Azure Blockchain Service pricing&#xA;Customers are doing great things with blockchain on Azure&#xA;GE Aviation&#xA;J.P. Morgan&#xA;Singapore Airlines&#xA;Xbox&#xA;Starbucks&#xA;Soaring to new heights with blockchain&#xA;&#xA;GE Aviation uses blockchain to streamline tracking of aircraft parts from factory to flight.&#xA;&#xA;Read the story&#xA;&#xA;GE Aviation&#xA;Start building with Azure Blockchain Service&#xA;Get instant access and a $200 credit when you sign up for an Azure free account.&#xA;Deploy Azure Blockchain Service using quickstart resources from the Azure engineering team.&#xA;Create smart contracts using the Visual Studio Code Extension and the Azure Blockchain Development Kit.&#xA;Tutorials, sample code, and app development guidance&#xA;5 minute quickstarts&#xA;Quickly deploy your first blockchain network through the Azure portal or Azure CLI.&#xA;Easily configure your transaction nodes’ security access through the Azure portal or Azure CLI.&#xA;Configure blockchain data manager to capture, transform, and deliver blockchain data to destinations of your choosing.&#xA;Explore cloud development patterns&#xA;&#xA;Watch these Block Talk episodes to learn how to build and configure your blockchain workloads.&#xA;&#xA;Deploy and configure your blockchain network&#xA;Write and test smart contracts with Visual Studio Code&#xA;Send data to the ledger with our dev kit&#xA;Publish events and ledger data to consuming apps&#xA;Accelerate development with code samples&#xA;&#xA;Connect any user interface, integrate with existing systems, and simplify smart contract DevOps using the Azure Blockchain Development Kit.&#xA;&#xA;Get started with sample smart contracts&#xA;Extend your application to read to/write from any system&#xA;Learn about smart contract DevOps&#xA;Azure Blockchain Service updates, blogs, and announcements&#xA;MAY 11, 2020&#xA;Office Licensing Service and Azure Cosmos DB part 2: Improved performance and availability&#xA;Parul Matah, Azure Cosmos DB&#xA;MAY 11, 2020&#xA;Office Licensing Service and Azure Cosmos DB part 1: Migrating the production workload&#xA;Parul Matah, Azure Cosmos DB&#xA;JANUARY 30, 2020&#xA;Hyperledger Fabric on Azure Kubernetes Service Marketplace template&#xA;Ramya Vastrad, Program Manager&#xA;NOVEMBER 6, 2019&#xA;Accelerating blockchain adoption in the enterprise&#xA;Matthew Kerner, General Manager, Microsoft Azure&#xA;OCTOBER 23, 2019&#xA;Introducing Corda Enterprise on Azure Blockchain Service&#xA;Marc Mercuri, Principal Program Manager, Blockchain Engineering&#xA;SEPTEMBER 24, 2019&#xA;12 TB VMs, Expanded SAP partnership on Blockchain, Azure Monitor for SAP Solutions&#xA;Girish Bablani, Corporate Vice President, Microsoft Azure&#xA;Frequently asked questions about Azure Blockchain Service&#xA;What is the difference between Basic and Standard?&#xA;What kind of support will I get with Azure Blockchain Service?&#xA;Can I use it with Workbench?&#xA;How can I send data to and from the ledger?&#xA;Where can I build my smart contracts?">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Blockchain/AzureBlockchain.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
