<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureMaps"
    id="75be7d26-04d8-4e35-a723-d9c03b8e05c7"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/azure-maps/&#xA;Azure Maps&#xA;Geospatial APIs to add maps, spatial analytics, and mobility solutions to your apps&#xA;&#xA;Put location intelligence to work for your enterprise&#xA;Create location-aware web and mobile applications using simple and secure geospatial services, APIs, and SDKs in Azure. Deliver seamless experiences based on geospatial data with built-in location intelligence from world-class mobility technology partners.&#xA;&#xA;Watch the overview video to learn how enterprises around the world are using Azure Maps—and how you can start using it today.&#xA;&#xA;Get world-class location and mobility technology&#xA;&#xA;Create your solutions using real-time location intelligence powered by world-class mobility technology partners TomTom and Moovit. Easily integrate advanced location and mobility capabilities into your applications with geospatial services that are native to Azure Maps.&#xA;&#xA;Build location intelligence solutions for IoT and AI&#xA;&#xA;Develop secure, scalable IoT and AI solutions with dynamic, location-based services. Enable everything from vehicle routing, traffic simulation, and asset tracking services to POI details and satellite imagery analysis.&#xA;Create rich data visualizations for your web and mobile apps&#xA;&#xA;Manage and customize your data representations with multiple map layers, such as heatmaps, image layers, and HTML markers. Select from rich visual imagery styles, including satellite, grayscale, and shaded relief tiles.&#xA;Use Azure Maps with open source and other familiar map controls&#xA;&#xA;Build your location-aware solutions with a seamless development experience. Easily integrate open source and other map controls, including OpenLayers, Leaflet, and Cesium, as well as Open Geospatial Consortium standards, such as GeoJSON and KML.&#xA;&#xA;Search&#xA;Create apps that provide details about nearby points of interest (POI), render locations on a map, and geocode (or reverse geocode) addresses to get corresponding latitude/longitude coordinates.&#xA;&#xA;Traffic&#xA;Develop mobility solutions that improve travel time and avoid gridlock. Offer multiple alternate routes around traffic jams, insight into the length of the backup and the time it takes to get through it, and a faster travel experience during rush hour.&#xA;&#xA;Maps&#xA;Integrate clear, easy-to-read maps into your solutions with the JavaScript Map Control or the Render API. The maps update dynamically, so your customers get constantly refreshed information. Build web and mobile apps with web and Android SDKs.&#xA;&#xA;Routing&#xA;Present the shortest or fastest routes available—to multiple destinations at a time—or provide specialized routes and facts for walkers, bicyclists, and commercial vehicles. Optimize route calculations with isochrones, matrix routing, and batch routing.&#xA;&#xA;Time zones&#xA;Make it easy for users to see what time it is anywhere in the world. Select a location to find the time zone, its offset to Coordinated Universal Time (UTC), and daylight saving time updates.&#xA;&#xA;Geolocation Preview&#xA;Look up the country of an IP address. Customize content and services based on user location and gain insight on customer geographic distribution.&#xA;&#xA;Spatial operations&#xA;Enhance your location intelligence with a library of common geospatial mathematical calculations, including geofencing, closest point, great circle distance, and buffers.&#xA;&#xA;Data Service Preview&#xA;Upload and store geospatial data for use with spatial operations or image composition to reduce latency, increase productivity, and enable new scenarios within your applications.&#xA;&#xA;Mobility Preview&#xA;Provide real-time location intelligence on nearby public transit services, including stops, route information, and travel time estimations.&#xA;&#xA;Weather Service Preview&#xA;Obtain current weather conditions, weather forecast, and weather along a route to enable weather based decisions within your applications.&#xA;&#xA;Creator Preview&#xA;Create and publish your maps maintaining control of design, distribution, scale and access by converting various mapping file formats to be used in conjunction with Azure Maps and other Azure services.&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Web/AzureMaps.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
