<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Xamarin"
    id="a0c118c7-6c4e-4c27-95c6-7dba2b7dacde"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/features/xamarin/&#xA;Xamarin with Azure&#xA;Create powerful and scalable native mobile apps with .NET and Azure&#xA;&#xA;Mobile apps with .NET&#xA;Xamarin is a free, cross-platform and open-source mobile-app platform for building native Android and iOS apps using .NET and C#. With Xamarin and Azure, you can get started quickly using various services, from authentication to storage and Azure Cognitive Services, to provide an immersive experience tailored to your users’ needs.&#xA;Get full access to device capabilities and platform-specific hardware. Xamarin apps are compiled for native performance&#xA;Share more than 95 percent of your code across platforms with Xamarin.Forms and the MVVM design pattern&#xA;Azure provides the scalable, efficient, versatile back end—from storage to authentication, intelligent services, and beyond&#xA;Available on any platform with the tools that provide a great .NET development experience for both Windows and Mac&#xA;&#xA;Develop on macOS and Windows&#xA;&#xA;Xamarin is an open-source platform used to create mobile apps for a variety of devices using C# or F#. Visual Studio and Visual Studio for Mac provide world-class refactoring and code cleanup capabilities and IntelliSense to increase developer productivity. And they come with powerful debugging capabilities for building, deploying, and debugging apps on emulators or simulators or directly on physical devices.&#xA;&#xA;Visual Studio tools for Xamarin&#xA;&#xA;Build captivating cross-platform apps&#xA;&#xA;Xamarin.Forms is an open-source, mobile-UI framework for building iOS and Android apps with .NET from a single, shared codebase. Maximize productivity and efficiency while providing a consistent look and feel across platforms. Xamarin allows you to access platform-specific APIs and reuse existing C/C++ libraries to write mobile apps and games powered by .NET and Azure.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about Xamarin.Forms&#xA;&#xA;Best-in-class DevOps tools&#xA;&#xA;Implement a CI/CD solution and add monitoring and reporting for your mobile apps using your favorite DevOps tools—and speed up the development process throughout your app’s lifecycle. Choose from the most productive development tools, including GitHub, Azure DevOps, and Visual Studio App Center. These are all designed to help you build, test, deploy, and monitor your apps so that you can focus on what really matters—creating amazing mobile experiences for your users.&#xA;&#xA;CI/CD with Azure DevOps&#xA;&#xA;Intelligent apps with Azure Cognitive Services&#xA;&#xA;Transform the ways in which your users interact with your apps and their environment by adding intelligent algorithms. Infuse your apps with advanced capabilities that see, hear, speak to, understand, and interpret users’ needs through natural methods of communication. Use the SDKs or REST APIs to tap into the intelligent cloud with only a few lines of code.&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Mobile/xamarin_logo.jpg"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
