<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureEventGrid"
    id="6af4a579-86ea-49f1-994a-151195d00463"
    documentation="Get reliable event delivery at massive scale&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/event-grid/&#xA;Use Event Grid to power your event-driven and serverless apps&#xA;Simplify your event-based apps with Event Grid, a single service for managing routing of all events from any source to any destination. Designed for high availability, consistent performance, and dynamic scale, Event Grid lets you focus on your app logic rather than infrastructure.&#xA;&#xA;Simplify event delivery&#xA;Eliminate polling—and the associated cost and latency. With Event Grid, event publishers are decoupled from event subscribers using a pub/sub model and simple HTTP-based event delivery, allowing you to build scalable serverless applications, microservices, and distributed systems.&#xA;&#xA;Build reliable cloud applications&#xA;Gain massive scale, dynamically, while getting near-real-time notifications for changes you’re interested in. Build better, more reliable applications through reactive programming, capitalizing on guaranteed event delivery and the high availability of the cloud.&#xA;&#xA;Focus on product innovation&#xA;Develop richer application scenarios by connecting multiple possible sources and destinations of events. Your business logic can be triggered by virtually all Azure services, as well as custom sources. Fully managed event delivery, intelligent filtering, and the ability to send events to multiple recipients at once allow you to focus on solving business problems rather than infrastructure.&#xA;&#xA;Example uses for Event Grid&#xA;&#xA;Serverless application architectures: Event Grid connects data sources and event handlers. For example, use Event Grid to instantly trigger a serverless function to run image analysis each time a new photo is added to a blob storage container.&#xA;&#xA;Ops automation: Event Grid allows you to speed automation and simplify policy enforcement. For example, Event Grid can notify Azure Automation when a virtual machine is created, or a SQL Database is spun up. These events can be used to automatically check that service configurations are compliant, put metadata into operations tools, tag virtual machines, or file work items.&#xA;&#xA;Application integration: Event Grid connects your app with other services. For example, create an application topic to send your app’s event data to Event Grid and take advantage of its reliable delivery, advanced routing, and direct integration with Azure. Alternatively, you can use Event Grid with Logic Apps to process data anywhere, without writing code.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Integration/AzureEventGrid.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
