<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDataShare"
    id="9ce64bd5-bb7f-4ab0-84b7-60eb34ea9d08"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/data-share/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Data Share&#xA;A simple and safe service for sharing big data&#xA;&#xA;Easily share data on your terms&#xA;Share data, in any format and any size, from multiple sources with other organizations. Easily control what you share, who receives your data, and the terms of use. Data Share provides full visibility into your data sharing relationships with a user-friendly interface. Share data in just a few clicks, or build your own application using the REST API.&#xA;&#xA;Serverless code-free data sharing service that requires no infrastructure setup or management&#xA;Intuitive interface to govern all your data sharing relationships&#xA;Automated data sharing processes for productivity and predictability&#xA;Secure data sharing service that uses underlying Azure security measures&#xA;&#xA;Easily share data the way you want&#xA;&#xA;Share structured and unstructured data from multiple Azure data stores with other organizations in just a few clicks. There’s no infrastructure to set up or manage, no SAS keys are required, and sharing is all code-free. You control data access and set terms of use aligned with your enterprise policies. Use snapshot-based sharing to copy data from the data provider, or use in-place sharing to refer to data in the provider’s account.&#xA;&#xA;Govern your data shares for safer sharing&#xA;&#xA;Easily and efficiently track and manage your data sharing relationships using an intuitive, user-friendly interface. See who you have shared data with and when the data is accepted. Stop future updates from flowing through at any time.&#xA;&#xA;Expand analytical datasets for enhanced insights&#xA;&#xA;Combine internal data with partner data for new insights. Share and receive data in any format to or from Azure Synapse Analytics, Azure SQL Database, Azure Blob Storage, Azure Data Lake Storage and Azure Data Explorer. Data Share will support more Azure data stores in the future.&#xA;&#xA;Data Share security&#xA;&#xA;Data Share uses underlying Azure security measures to help protect your data.&#xA;Control access at the account resource level to help ensure only authorized users can access the data.&#xA;Data is encrypted in transit, and metadata is encrypted at rest and in transit.&#xA;Data Share uses managed identities for Azure resources and integrates with Azure Active Directory (AAD) to manage credentials and permissions.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Storage/AzureDataShare.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
