<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureFunction"
    id="b56281fb-099e-4c10-8d08-fc5d7a73e587"
    documentation="Azure Functions: More than just event-driven serverless compute&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/functions/&#xA;&#xA;Accelerate and simplify application development with serverless compute: Develop more efficiently with Functions, an event-driven serverless compute platform that can also solve complex orchestration problems. Build and debug locally without additional setup, deploy and operate at scale in the cloud, and integrate services using triggers and bindings.&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/microsoft-named-a-leader-in-the-forrester-new-wave-functions-as-a-service-platforms/&#xA;&#xA;Automated and flexible scaling based on your workload volume, keeping the focus on adding value instead of managing infrastructure&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Integrated programming model based on triggers and bindings that help you respond to events and seamlessly connect to other services&#xA;&#xA;End-to-end development experience, from building and debugging to deploying and monitoring with integrated tools and built-in DevOps capabilities&#xA;&#xA;Variety of programming languages and hosting options—always pick the best one for each scenario and quickly adjust to meet business needs&#xA;&#xA;Improve your end-to-end development experience&#xA;Take advantage of a complete, end-to-end development experience with Functions—from building and debugging locally on major platforms like Windows, macOS, and Linux to deploying and monitoring in the cloud. Use Functions extensions and templates on Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code for a faster and more efficient development on your local machine, fully integrated with the whole Azure platform. Develop using your favorite code editor and the Azure Functions Core Tools. Set up continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) with Azure Pipelines, and get intelligent and proactive insights about the performance of applications in production from Azure Monitor.&#xA;&#xA;Simplify complex orchestration challenges resolution&#xA;Serverless functions are meant to be short-lived and stateless—until you need them to solve stateful problems. Remove this limitation in a fully managed way without provisioning more resources, just by coding your workflow definition. Simplify complex, stateful coordination requirements programmatically in event-driven applications with the Durable Functions extension. Use your functions also on declarative workflows that can take advantage of over 250 connectors with Azure Logic Apps.&#xA;&#xA;Connect other services without hard-coding integrations for faster solutions development&#xA;Write only the code that truly matters to your business. Save coding time with a programming model based on triggers and bindings that enable your serverless applications to respond to events and connect to other services seamlessly. Build more scalable and stable event-driven applications with a microservices-friendly approach using Functions.&#xA;&#xA;Build once, deploy anywhere&#xA;Not all applications are the same, and one hosting plan won't fit them all. Pick the Functions plan that matches your business needs, and deploy the same code to multiple targets - from pay-per-execution in the cloud to your Kubernetes cluster or IoT devices for edge computing.&#xA;&#xA;Develop your way&#xA;Start coding right away with the technology stack you already know and love, no new languages or frameworks to learn. Pick the programming languages you like best for each unique scenario—from web apps and APIs with .NET, Node.js or Java, to Machine Learning workflows with Python or cloud automation with PowerShell.&#xA;&#xA;Create reliable serverless applications with built-in security and monitoring&#xA;&#xA;Monitor and analyze code performance with Azure Application Insights. Spot bottlenecks and failure hotspots across all components of your application using application maps with distributed tracing from Azure Monitor.&#xA;Source application settings with full control over access policies and audit history—without making code changes—using Azure Key Vault.&#xA;Isolate networks through virtual network connectivity on the Functions Premium plan, enabling outbound traffic into a secured virtual network gating incoming traffic and defining app restrictions.&#xA;Configure managed identities at the service level to let applications easily access other resources protected by Azure Active Directory.&#xA;Grant access to your application using built-in authentication with Azure Active Directory, Microsoft account, and external providers such as Twitter, Facebook, and Google">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Compute/AzureFunction.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
