<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureKubernetesService"
    id="b11c036f-484e-4af6-a50b-6c884e74aae5"
    documentation="Highly available, secure, and fully managed Kubernetes service&#xA;&#xA;Ship faster, operate with ease, and scale confidently: Deploy and manage containerized applications more easily with a fully managed Kubernetes service. Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) offers serverless Kubernetes, an integrated continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) experience, and enterprise-grade security and governance. Unite your development and operations teams on a single platform to rapidly build, deliver, and scale applications with confidence.&#xA;&#xA;Elastic provisioning of capacity without the need to manage the infrastructure, and with the ability to add event-driven autoscaling and triggers through KEDA&#xA;&#xA;Faster end-to-end development experience with Azure Dev Spaces including integration with Visual Studio Code Kubernetes tools, Azure DevOps, and Azure Monitor&#xA;&#xA;Advanced identity and access management using Azure Active Directory, and dynamic rules enforcement across multiple clusters with Azure Policy&#xA;&#xA;Available in more regions than any other cloud provider&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Accelerate containerized application development: Easily define, deploy, debug, and upgrade even the most complex Kubernetes applications, and automatically containerize your applications. Develop and test microservices-based applications without mocking up dependencies using Dev Spaces.&#xA;Add a full CI/CD pipeline to your AKS clusters with automated routine tasks, and set up a canary deployment strategy in just a few clicks. Detect failures early and optimize your pipelines with deep traceability into your deployments.&#xA;Gain visibility into your environment with control-plane telemetry, log aggregation, and container health, accessible in the Azure portal and automatically configured for AKS clusters.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Increased operational efficiency&#xA;Rely on built-in automated provisioning, repair, monitoring, and scaling. This checkbox-like experience helps you get up and running quickly and minimizes infrastructure maintenance.&#xA;&#xA;Easily provision fully managed clusters with automatically configured monitoring capabilities based on Prometheus.&#xA;Use Azure Advisor to optimize your Kubernetes deployments with real-time, personalized recommendations based on our knowledge from working with thousands of enterprise customers.&#xA;Elastically add compute capacity with serverless Kubernetes, in seconds, without worrying about managing the infrastructure.&#xA;Achieve higher availability and protect applications from datacenter failures by using redundancies across availability zones.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Build on an enterprise-grade, more secure foundation&#xA;Dynamically enforce guardrails defined in Azure Policy at the time of deployment or as part of CI/CD workflows. Deploy only validated images to your private container registry.&#xA;Get fine-grained identity and access control to Kubernetes resources, from cluster to containers, using Azure Active Directory.&#xA;Enforce pod security context and configure across multiple clusters with Azure Policy. Track, validate, and reconfigure easily. Get compliance reports for the entire environment with pod-level granularity.&#xA;Achieve superior security with a hardened operating system image, automated patching, and disks encrypted using your own keys. Automate threat detection and remediation using advanced analytics from Azure Security Center.&#xA;Use Azure Private Link to limit Kubernetes API server (control plane) access to your Azure virtual network. Help secure communication paths between namespaces and nodes with user-defined network policy.&#xA;Get the definitive guide to securing Kubernetes&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Run any workload in the cloud, at the edge, or as a hybrid&#xA;Orchestrate any type of workload running in the environment of your choice. Whether you want to move .NET applications to Windows Server containers, modernize Java applications in Linux containers, or run microservices applications in the public cloud, at the edge, or in hybrid environments, Azure has the solution for you.&#xA;&#xA;Learn about the Kubernetes core concepts and apply best practices in production.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Containers/AzureKubernetesService.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
