<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDDoSProtection"
    id="6e9ce0ae-38a3-423f-b16c-f6362680a25c"
    documentation="https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/ddos-protection-overview&#xA;&#xA;Distributed denial of service (DDoS) attacks are some of the largest availability and security concerns facing customers that are moving their applications to the cloud. A DDoS attack attempts to exhaust an application's resources, making the application unavailable to legitimate users. DDoS attacks can be targeted at any endpoint that is publicly reachable through the internet.&#xA;Azure DDoS protection, combined with application design best practices, provide defense against DDoS attacks. Azure DDoS protection provides the following service tiers:&#xA;Basic: Automatically enabled as part of the Azure platform. Always-on traffic monitoring, and real-time mitigation of common network-level attacks, provide the same defenses utilized by Microsoft's online services. The entire scale of Azure's global network can be used to distribute and mitigate attack traffic across regions. Protection is provided for IPv4 and IPv6 Azure public IP addresses.&#xA;Standard: Provides additional mitigation capabilities over the Basic service tier that are tuned specifically to Azure Virtual Network resources. DDoS Protection Standard is simple to enable, and requires no application changes. Protection policies are tuned through dedicated traffic monitoring and machine learning algorithms. Policies are applied to public IP addresses associated to resources deployed in virtual networks, such as Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, and Azure Service Fabric instances, but this protection does not apply to App Service Environments. Real-time telemetry is available through Azure Monitor views during an attack, and for history. Rich attack mitigation analytics are available via diagnostic settings. Application layer protection can be added through the Azure Application Gateway Web Application Firewall or by installing a 3rd party firewall from Azure Marketplace. Protection is provided for IPv4 and IPv6 Azure public IP addresses.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Networking/AzureAzureDDoSProtection.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
