<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureNotificationHubs"
    id="e83c185d-c007-44fb-8b63-9a1083b11d5f"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/notification-hubs/&#xA;Notification Hubs&#xA;Send push notifications to any platform from any back end&#xA;&#xA;Reach all major platforms—iOS, Android, Windows, Kindle, Baidu&#xA;Use any back end, in the cloud or on-premises&#xA;Fast broadcast push to millions of mobile devices with single API call&#xA;Tailor push notifications by customer, language, and location&#xA;Dynamically define and notify customer segments&#xA;Scale instantly to millions of mobile devices&#xA;&#xA;Fast broadcast to millions of devices&#xA;Azure Notification Hubs is a massively scalable mobile push notification engine for quickly sending millions of notifications to iOS, Android, Windows, or Kindle devices, working with APNs (Apple Push Notification service), GCM (Google Cloud Messaging), WNS (Windows Push Notification Service), MPNS (Microsoft Push Notification Service), and more. Tailor your notifications to specific customers—or entire audiences—with just a few lines of code, and do it across any platform.&#xA;&#xA;Works with any back end&#xA;Notification Hubs is flexible enough to plug into any back end—Microsoft .NET, PHP, Java, Node.js—whether it’s located on-premises or in the cloud. This makes it easier to instantly update your mobile apps and engage your customers.&#xA;&#xA;Target any audience with dynamic tags&#xA;Broadcast push notifications to everyone at once or target specific customer devices using the Notification Hubs tagging feature. Tags let you segment customers based on activity, interest, location, or preference, so you deliver the right content to the right person at the right time.&#xA;&#xA;Make localization easier with templates&#xA;If your app covers multiple markets, the templates feature of Notification Hubs gives you a handy way to send localized push notifications, so you’re speaking to customers in their languages. Templates also eliminate the hassle of storing the localization settings for each customer or creating hundreds of tags.&#xA;&#xA;Designed for massive scale&#xA;Quickly scale to millions of mobile devices and billions of notifications without re-architecting or sharding. Notification Hubs automatically handles the infrastructure necessary to scale your message to every active device with low latency.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Mobile/AzureNotificationHubs.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
