<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureFrontDoorService"
    id="f9b1057c-e404-4cd5-864e-06b3d2d0b71b"
    documentation="Azure Front Door&#xA;Scalable and secure entry point for fast delivery of your global applications&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/frontdoor/&#xA;SSL offload and application acceleration at the edge close to end users&#xA;Web Application Firewall (WAF) and DDoS Protection&#xA;Global HTTP load balancing with instant failover&#xA;Central control plane for traffic orchestration&#xA;Actionable insights about your users and back ends&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Globally distributed microservice applications&#xA;Easily join your distributed microservice architectures into a single global application using HTTP load balancing and path-based routing rules. Automate turning up new regions and scale-out with API-driven global actions, and independent fault-tolerance to your back end microservices in Azure—or anywhere.&#xA;Dynamic applications with global reach&#xA;Deliver and protect your global application close to your end users with a &quot;battle-tested&quot; service built on world-class Microsoft Global Network infrastructure. Always keep your traffic on the best path to your app, improve your service scale, reduce latency, and increase throughput for your global users with edge load balancing and application acceleration.&#xA;Global, real-time performance and availability for your app or API&#xA;Flexibly route your users to the closest available backend—with instant failover—for changes in availability or on-the-path performance from your users to your backend. Front Door supports different load balancing algorithms to better manage your back end load, including round-robin, weighted round-robin, active/standby configurations, and cookie-based session affinity.&#xA;Scale up your global application&#xA;Offload SSL and domain management at the edge while accelerating dynamic content to improve agility and scale for your app—and performance for your users.&#xA;Protect your app from attacks&#xA;Stop network and application layer attacks at the edge with Web Application Firewall and DDoS Protection. Harden your service using Microsoft managed rule sets and author your own rules for custom protection of your app.&#xA;Centralized traffic orchestration view&#xA;Easily manage domain mapping and traffic to your microservice backends using one central, global dashboard.&#xA;Actionable insights about your users and backends&#xA;&#xA;Get insights about where your users are connecting from and the quality of their experience, and select the optimal regions for your Azure back ends.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Networking/AzureFrontDoorService.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
