<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureIotCentral"
    id="2764ffc4-958d-4336-ba78-13f5486ef316"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/iot-central/&#xA;Azure IoT Central&#xA;Proof of concept isn’t your endgame. We’ll help you build industry-leading solutions with a hosted IoT application platform.&#xA;&#xA;Azure IoT Central is your IoT app platform&#xA;Azure IoT Central is highly secure, scales with your business as it grows, ensures your investments are repeatable, and integrates with your existing business apps.&#xA;&#xA;Highly secure&#xA;Enterprise-grade&#xA;Predictable pricing&#xA;Industry-focused&#xA;Azure IoT Central updates  &#xA;&#xA;Get connected&#xA;Azure IoT Central connects your IoT devices to the cloud faster than any other platform. Find new devices matched to your solution in the Azure Certified for IoT device catalog&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Stay connected&#xA;We understand how hard it is to keep devices connected and healthy. Centralized management helps you reconfigure and update them&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Transform&#xA;Our connectors and extensibility APIs bridge the gap between your business applications and IoT—providing a direct connection between IoT data and your decision makers&#xA;&#xA;Transform your business with our IoT app platform&#xA;From launch to production, rapidly build enterprise-grade IoT applications on a secure, reliable, and scalable infrastructure.&#xA;&#xA;Jump-start&#xA;&#xA;Connect&#xA;&#xA;Manage&#xA;&#xA;Scale&#xA;&#xA;Extend&#xA;&#xA;Monetize&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Industry-specific app templates for retail, energy, healthcare, and government help you get up and running.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Build secure and scalable IoT enterprise solutions&#xA;Can your IoT solution grow with you? Are you protecting data on devices and in the cloud? Azure IoT Central is the only app platform that’s built with the properties of highly secure and scalable IoT solutions.&#xA;&#xA;Read the white paper&#xA;Retail&#xA;Health&#xA;Energy&#xA;Government&#xA;Tackle common IoT scenarios across industries&#xA;Ready to build? Get ahead in your market and transform your business with our growing selection of IoT app templates for common industry scenarios. Enrich your offerings by integrating with other industry technologies and partner solutions. All while keeping your data and brand in your control.&#xA;&#xA;Explore our industry app templates&#xA;Rest easy with industry-leading security&#xA;&#xA;Microsoft invests more than USD 1 billion annually on cybersecurity research and development.&#xA;We employ more than 3,500 security experts completely dedicated to your data security and privacy.&#xA;Azure has more compliance certifications than any other cloud provider. View the comprehensive list.&#xA;Learn more about security on Azure&#xA;&#xA;Simple, predictable pricing&#xA;No upfront cost&#xA;No termination fees&#xA;Pay only for what you need&#xA;Get pricing details">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/InternetOfThings/azure_iot_central.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
