<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureStreamAnalytics"
    id="95acc680-1ba6-4748-a2e6-387651edbb7f"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/stream-analytics/&#xA;Azure Stream Analytics&#xA;Serverless real-time analytics, from the cloud to the edge&#xA;Deliver powerful insights from your streaming data with ease, in real time&#xA;Discover Azure Stream Analytics, the easy-to-use, real-time analytics service that is designed for mission-critical workloads. Build an end-to-end serverless streaming pipeline with just a few clicks. Go from zero to production in minutes using SQL—easily extensible with custom code and built-in machine learning capabilities for more advanced scenarios. Run your most demanding workloads with the confidence of a financially backed SLA.&#xA;&#xA;End-to-end analytics pipeline that is production-ready in minutes with familiar SQL syntax and extensible with JavaScript and C# custom code&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Rapid scalability with elastic capacity to build robust streaming data pipelines and analyze millions of events at subsecond latencies&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Hybrid architectures for stream processing with the ability to run the same queries in the cloud and on the edge&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Enterprise-grade reliability with built-in recovery and built-in machine learning capabilities for advanced scenarios&#xA;&#xA;Build streaming pipelines in minutes&#xA;Run complex analytics with no need to learn new processing frameworks or provision virtual machines (VMs) or clusters. Use familiar SQL language that is extensible with JavaScript and C# custom code for more advanced use cases. Easily enable scenarios like low-latency dashboarding, streaming ETL, and real-time alerting with one-click integration across sources and sinks.&#xA;&#xA;Get started with real-time analytics on Azure&#xA;&#xA;Run mission-critical workloads with subsecond latencies&#xA;Get guaranteed, “exactly once” event processing with 99.9% availability and built-in recovery capabilities. Easily set up a continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI-CD) pipeline and achieve subsecond latencies on your most demanding workloads.&#xA;&#xA;Learn how to deploy an Azure Stream Analytics job with CI-CD&#xA;Deploy in the cloud and on the edge&#xA;Bring real-time insights and analytics capabilities closer to where your data originates. Enable new scenarios with true hybrid architectures for stream processing and run the same query in the cloud or on the edge.&#xA;&#xA;Learn more about real-time analytics on the edge&#xA;&#xA;Build a secure streaming solution with enhanced security and compliance from Azure&#xA;&#xA;In-memory processing, with encrypted checkpointing&#xA;Encryption of all incoming and outgoing communications&#xA;Meets international and industry-specific security and compliance standards, including HIPAA, HITRUST, CSA STAR, and ISO/SOC requirements">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Analytics/AzureStreamAnalytics.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
