<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureDataLakeStorage"
    id="58a48ef3-8ce7-4264-b2d1-c3b5389b9cc9"
    documentation="Azure Data Lake Storage&#xA;Massively scalable, secure data lake functionality built on Azure Blob Storage&#xA;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/storage/data-lake-storage/&#xA;&#xA;Get powerful data lake functionality at cloud scale&#xA;Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 is a highly scalable and cost-effective data lake solution for big data analytics. It combines the power of a high-performance file system with massive scale and economy to help you speed your time to insight. Data Lake Storage Gen2 extends Azure Blob Storage capabilities and is optimized for analytics workloads. Data Lake Storage Gen2 is the most comprehensive data lake available.&#xA;&#xA;Fast&#xA;Test models faster with a Hadoop-compatible file system that supports atomic file and folder operations and is optimized to execute jobs at lightning speed.&#xA;&#xA;Scalable&#xA;Extend the global scale, durability, and performance of Azure Blob Storage, and get support for massive storage accounts.&#xA;&#xA;Secure&#xA;Meet the most stringent enterprise data security requirements with tools and resources like POSIX-compliant, fine-grained ACL support, object store security with at-rest encryption, Azure Active Directory integration, and storage account firewalls.&#xA;&#xA;Cost-effective&#xA;Get data lake functionality at cloud object store pricing levels. Data Lake Storage Gen2 provides the same lifecycle policy management and object-level tiering that’s built into Blob Storage.&#xA;&#xA;Fast&#xA;Test models faster with a Hadoop-compatible file system that supports atomic file and folder operations and is optimized to execute jobs at lightning speed.&#xA;&#xA;Scalable&#xA;Extend the global scale, durability, and performance of Azure Blob Storage, and get support for massive storage accounts.&#xA;&#xA;Secure&#xA;Meet the most stringent enterprise data security requirements with tools and resources like POSIX-compliant, fine-grained ACL support, object store security with at-rest encryption, Azure Active Directory integration, and storage account firewalls.&#xA;&#xA;Cost-effective&#xA;Get data lake functionality at cloud object store pricing levels. Data Lake Storage Gen2 provides the same lifecycle policy management and object-level tiering that’s built into Blob Storage.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Storage/AzureDataLakeStorage.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
