<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureCognitiveSearch"
    id="8c0351f7-23f9-4885-8445-292b18cad210"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/search/&#xA;Azure Cognitive Search&#xA;AI-powered cloud search service for mobile and web app development&#xA;&#xA;Uncover latent insights from all your content&#xA;Azure Cognitive Search is the only cloud search service with built-in AI capabilities that enrich all types of information to easily identify and explore relevant content at scale. Formerly known as Azure Search, it uses the same integrated Microsoft natural language stack that Bing and Office have used for more than a decade, and AI services across vision, language, and speech. Spend more time innovating and less time maintaining a complex cloud search solution.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Fully managed search as a service to reduce complexity and scale easily&#xA;Auto-complete, geospatial search, filtering, and faceting capabilities for a rich user experience&#xA;Built-in AI capabilities including OCR, key phrase extraction, and named entity recognition to unlock insights&#xA;Flexible integration of custom models, classifiers, and rankers to fit your domain-specific needs&#xA;&#xA;        &#xA;Start, maintain, and scale with minimal investment&#xA;&#xA;Deploy a search index quickly and avoid operational maintenance. This fully managed cloud search service reduces the complexity of data ingestion and index creation by integrating with popular Azure storage solutions and offering index functionality exposed through a simple REST API or .NET SDK. Deploy a fully configured search service with intuitive user experiences such as scoring, faceting, suggestions, synonyms, and geo-search—all while avoiding the operational overhead needed to debug index corruption, monitor service availability, or manually scale during traffic fluctuations.&#xA;&#xA;Create searchable content using integrated AI&#xA;&#xA;Take advantage of Azure AI speech, vision, and language services to transform raw, unstructured information into searchable content. Easily orchestrate AI services that bring structure to your data before it’s indexed by defining your own Cognitive Search skillset. Applying AI capabilities such as OCR, translation, key phrase extraction, location, people, and organization detection is as simple as checking a box in the Cognitive Search portal.&#xA;&#xA;Customize to meet goals and industry requirements&#xA;&#xA;Extend the Cognitive Search platform to match your specific business goals and industry requirements. Better understand your data using custom models and classifiers, such as legal clause classifiers or manufacturing material identifiers, available in any language or framework. After you’ve deployed your cloud search service, quickly adjust your search results using rich, custom-tuned ranking models to tie your results to your business goals.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Web/AzureCognitiveSearch.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
