<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="WebApplicationFirewall"
    id="1759cb51-3b00-49e7-905e-9b50593f25d4"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/web-application-firewall/&#xA;Azure Web Application Firewall&#xA;A cloud-native web application firewall (WAF) service that provides powerful protection for web apps&#xA;Get better security for your web applications&#xA;Help protect your web apps from malicious attacks and common web vulnerabilities, such as SQL injection and cross-site scripting. With the cloud-native Azure web application firewall (WAF) service, deploy in minutes and only pay for what you use.&#xA;Protection for the top 10 Open Web Application Security Project (OWASP) security vulnerabilities&#xA;Deploy in minutes with improved security in a single click&#xA;Customized rules to meet your web app security requirements&#xA;Near real-time visibility and alerts through Azure Monitor&#xA;&#xA;Play VideoPlay&#x9;&#xA;Current Time 0:00&#xA;Loaded: 0%Progress: 0%Seekbar Handle&#xA;/&#xA;Duration Time 5:46&#xA;Mute&#xA;Fullscreen&#xA;Enhance security with high availability and scale&#xA;&#xA;Optimize performance with Azure Web Application Firewall deployed with Azure Front Door. Increase throughput for your global users with edge load balancing and application acceleration. Optimize your web app for high availability and scalability—with built-in auto-scaling and zone redundancy.&#xA;&#xA;What is cloud-native Azure Network Security&#xA;Get managed rule sets to protect web apps&#xA;Help protect web applications from common vulnerabilities and exploits. Easily add and customize new rules to meet your application security requirements. Get a comprehensive list of web app firewall rule schemas and rules based on the OWASP core rule sets (CRS) 3.1/3.0.&#xA;&#xA;Read the documentation&#xA;Deploy quickly to keep web apps protected&#xA;Easily deploy within minutes with no additional software required. Configure and enable Azure Web Application Firewall on your web application. Then, centrally define your rules and reuse them across all the web apps that you need to protect. Learn how to customize web application firewall rules in the Azure portal.&#xA;&#xA;Read the documentation&#xA;Improve cost effectiveness for web app protection&#xA;Get competitive pricing for web application protection and pay only for what you use—with no minimum fees and no upfront commitments.">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Networking/AzureWebApplicationFirewall.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="40x40"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
