<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="SecurityCenter"
    id="4079cf4f-a86a-4723-968c-225847d6991e"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/security-center/&#xA;&#xA;Azure Security Center&#xA;Gain unmatched hybrid security management and threat protection&#xA;&#xA;Turn on protection you need&#xA;Microsoft uses a wide variety of physical, infrastructure, and operational controls to help secure Azure—but there are additional actions you need to take to help safeguard your workloads. Turn on Security Center to quickly strengthen your security posture and protect against threats.&#xA;Register now for the June 30, 2020 virtual event: Stay Ahead of Attacks with Azure Security Center.&#xA;Security posture management for your cloud workloads&#xA;&#xA;Quickly assess your security posture with Secure Score. This feature provides recommendations with numeric values to help you prioritize your responses.&#xA;Ensure you’re following best practices and fix common misconfigurations for Azure infrastructure as a service (IaaS) and platform as a service (PaaS) resources that may include:&#xA;&#xA;Failure to deploy system updates on virtual machines (VMs).&#xA;Unnecessary exposure to the Internet through public-facing endpoints.&#xA;Unencrypted data in transit or storage.&#xA;&#xA;When you address these, easily deploy Microsoft and partner solutions directly from the Azure portal.&#xA;Customize your security policy to focus on what you need to—for example, check for web application firewalls or storage encryption—and apply your policy to multiple Azure subscriptions. Gain visibility across your environment to verify compliance with regulatory requirements, such as CIS, PCI DSS, SOC, and ISO.&#xA;Get enhanced threat protection with Security Center Standard tier&#xA;Security Center gives you defense in depth with its ability to both detect and help protect against threats. Using machine learning to process trillions of signals across Microsoft services and systems, Security Center alerts you of threats to your environments, such as remote desktop protocol (RDP) brute-force attacks and SQL injections. And it provides actionable recommendations for mitigating these threats.&#xA;Standard Tier also provides features to help you reduce your attack surface area. Our more than 3,500 security experts use Standard tier and recommend that you do, too.&#xA;Protect your Linux and Windows servers&#xA;Protect your cloud-native applications&#xA;Protect your data&#xA;Protect your IoT Solution&#xA;&#xA;Quickly set up and extend security beyond Azure&#xA;Extend security posture management and threat protection to on-premises VMs.&#xA;Easily provision an agent to server workloads running on-premises.&#xA;Assess your security through a unified view across your hybrid cloud workloads.&#xA;Connect to existing tools and processes, like security information and event management (SIEM), or integrate partner security solutions.&#xA;Reduce investments and reallocate resources by using built-in first-party or third-party security controls.&#xA;How Security Center works&#xA;When you activate Security Center, a monitoring agent is deployed automatically into Azure virtual machines. For on-premises VMs, you manually deploy the agent. Security Center begins assessing the security state of all your VMs, networks, applications, and data.&#xA;Our analytics engines analyze the data and machine learning synthesizes it. Security Center provides recommendations and threat alerts for protecting your workloads. You’ll know right away if there’s been an attack or anomalous activity.&#xA;Aggregate your security information in an Azure Monitor workspace for big data querying capabilities. Alternatively, you can query your data through REST APIs, PowerShell cmdlets, or integration with an existing SIEM, such as Azure Sentinel.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Security/AzureSecurityCentre.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
