<archimate:TechnologyService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="AzureEventHub"
    id="6a45ff81-e9d6-495f-97ba-33417e58d3f9"
    documentation="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/event-hubs/&#xA;&#xA;Event Hubs&#xA;Simple, secure, and scalable real-time data ingestion&#xA;&#xA;Event Hubs is a fully managed, real-time data ingestion service that’s simple, trusted, and scalable. Stream millions of events per second from any source to build dynamic data pipelines and immediately respond to business challenges. Keep processing data during emergencies using the geo-disaster recovery and geo-replication features.&#xA;&#xA;Integrate seamlessly with other Azure services to unlock valuable insights. Allow existing Apache Kafka clients and applications to talk to Event Hubs without any code changes—you get a managed Kafka experience without having to manage your own clusters. Experience real-time data ingestion and microbatching on the same stream.&#xA;&#xA;Link to video&#xA;&#xA;Play VideoPlay&#x9;&#xA;Current Time 0:00&#xA;Loaded: 0%Progress: 0%Seekbar Handle&#xA;/&#xA;Duration Time 1:46&#xA;Mute&#xA;Fullscreen&#xA;Why choose Event Hubs?&#xA;&#xA;Focus on drawing insights from your data instead of managing infrastructure. Build real-time big data pipelines and respond to business challenges right away.&#xA;Simple&#xA;&#xA;Build real-time data pipelines with just a couple clicks. Seamlessly integrate with Azure data services to uncover insights faster.&#xA;&#xA;Secure&#xA;&#xA;Protect your real-time data. Event Hubs is certified by CSA STAR, ISO, SOC, GxP, HIPAA, HITRUST, and PCI.&#xA;&#xA;Scalable&#xA;&#xA;Adjust throughput dynamically based on your usage needs and pay only for what you use.&#xA;&#xA;Open&#xA;&#xA;Ingest data from anywhere and develop across platforms with support for popular protocols, including AMQP, HTTPS, and Apache Kafka.®&#xA;&#xA;Ingest millions of events per second&#xA;Continuously ingress data from hundreds of thousands of sources with low latency and configurable time retention.&#xA;Enable real-time and micro-batch processing concurrently&#xA;Seamlessly send data to Blob storage or Data Lake Storage for long-term retention or micro-batch processing with Event Hubs Capture.&#xA;Get a managed service with elastic scale&#xA;Easily scale from streaming megabytes of data to terabytes while keeping control over when and how much to scale.&#xA;Easily connect with the Apache Kafka ecosystem&#xA;Seamlessly connect Event Hubs with your Kafka applications and clients with Azure Event Hubs for Apache Kafka®.&#xA;Build a serverless streaming solution&#xA;Natively connect with Stream Analytics to build an end-to-end serverless streaming solution.&#xA;Serverless streaming with Event Hubs&#xA;&#xA;Build an end-to-end serverless streaming platform with Event Hubs and Stream Analytics&#xA;&#xA;">
  <properties
      key="icon"
      value="/Analytics/AzureEventHub.png"/>
  <properties
      key="icon size"
      value="50x50"/>
</archimate:TechnologyService>
